Thank you to Vapid Raven Warrior.
For the gifted subs.
Let's all turn to page 9 where we praise Vapid Raven Warrior.
Now together.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, man.
That's your six in total now.
I really appreciate it.
You have indeed been blessed my child.
It's good to see you all.
How's it going?
What are you guys up to, huh?
The holy can.
I like that.
Man, the can opening on with all the reverberation sounds awesome.
I should do that every time now.
I feel like it's so fitting for Noiter.
That game gives me churchy vibes, you know?
Like religious vibes.
What's up, Hive?
You just woke up?
Welcome to the stream.
Good to have you again.
Good and better since you're online.
Thank you, Rat Shadow.
I appreciate that.
That's very nice of you.
Popcorn time.
Oh yeah?
What time is it where you live?
Not that I'm judging.
Anytime is good time for popcorn.
Doing some Final Fantasy 14 while watching.
Man, there's a lot of those Final Fantasy games, huh?
Fucking 14?
I'm not judging so hard.
I'm judging.
My judge level is two right now out of 45.
On the low end for sure.
Finally able to make it first stream.
Welcome, Lymanate.
Good to see you.
Final Fantasy.
Oh, man.
I don't even remember if I left off in the middle of a run.
I think I did because I can, it says continue here.
It says continue, so let me just take a quick look.
Okay, so yeah.
Unfortunately, I didn't start, stop in the middle.
That's fine.
We get to start over fresh.
Hold on.
I'm gonna connect my keyboard, of course.
Otherwise, I can't play the game.
Really don't want to have to use a keyboard for a computer, but you know, if I have to, then fine.
I'll connect it.
Yeah, I'm jumping right in.
I'm just gonna play my game here.
Thank you so much again, Vapid Raven Warrior for the sub.
And also, I can't pronounce your name.
Oh, actually, I can't.
Creamy Mommy.
Thank you so much.
And Dexma.
I also see Ikasiki.
One of the first people who's up to this channel, actually.
Thank you so much, everybody.
Okay, I'm gonna close you guys down.
No offense.
And then I'm gonna head straight in.
What?
What was that sound just now?
Whoops!
Didn't mean to do that.
It is what it is.
I did that just now.
Alright, I'm gonna do this again.
It's the classic start here.
Can't go wrong with that, right?
Go grab some HP.
Make it a nice start for a nice run.
Dude, I'm gonna not die a single time today.
And not only that, I'm gonna get further than I've ever been today.
This run.
You don't believe me?
Watch.
Look at that smooth ass.
Operator here, number one.
I wonder if I can blow up that thing.
Oh, you know what?
I'm going on top of this.
Wait, what is... Why is there a tree here?
Did I fall down?
The hell?
Oh, I'm so good.
Oh, no, I'm not so good.
Okay, I am actually pretty good.
Hold on.
Get here.
Go.
Is that the gods being angry?
Oh, wait a minute.
Is that what happened that one time?
Did I maybe grab too many hearts?
You know, because we get the rumble from below, which sounds like some kind of demon.
Maybe I made them too angry, and then it said the gods are angry, right?
Whoops.
Reward me?
Yeah.
My curiosity has been rewarded.
Man, I want to be rewarded more for my curiosity.
I want to do other things like that.
That was such a fucking coincidence that I figured that out.
Like, if I hadn't tried that, there's a good chance I may never have figured that out.
So I need to try all kinds of weird things today.
Things that may not even make sense at first.
I'm just gonna try it.
You know?
I think it's a good habit.
This game is very unusual when it comes to, well, so far at least, to the secrets and stuff.
Okay, let's see what we have.
A decent wand.
I like it.
A good start here.
There's a wand right below me as well.
Ah, feels good to be back in this game.
God damn.
Feels real good.
I do wonder if I'm gonna get more lore.
And if there even is a cohesive story or world-building aspect to this, because I'm very intrigued by what I've seen so far.
I like the whole religious twist on these things, you know?
The gods are angry and stuff like that.
The deep rumble from below.
Man.
I love that sort of stuff.
Can't wait to see what happens when I get a little further.
So the furthest I've been so far is some kind of jungly area with the spiders.
And that was a... Oh man, if I get back there, I'm not gonna have melee immunity like I had last time.
I'm actually gonna die of... I don't even know how I'm gonna get through that area.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
That is gonna... Just because I hate spiders so much, I hate when they damage me, I hate when they get near me, touch me, do things to me.
I had immunity last time so I could sort of lack... Look at this guy in here.
You have been freed, sir!
God damn, you have some HP there.
You're gonna come up here?
Nice, look at that.
We're playing this so patiently and so smoothly.
Love it.
Fucking everything has been acided away.
Dissolve is the word for that.
Yikes!
Where did that gold come from?
Don't question it, just take it.
There's actually stuff up there it seems.
Kind of wanna check it out.
Oh also, whoa!
I have mud potion.
I can't use that I don't think to put out fires.
So the first order of business actually needs to be to find some more water.
Like a big pool of it.
It's actually one of the most important things.
Shit, that was a terrible thing.
Oh my god, what am I doing?
Yeah, this ain't going well.
What?
Okay, hold on.
Let me go from over here.
All right, I'm not gonna get up there.
That's fine.
I'm too angry now, I can't get in.
Water!
And hearts!
Oh my god, exactly what we need.
What if I put it in here?
See, why would I put mud in the water when I'm about to drink it?
Seems like a bad idea, right?
Not something you would do in real life.
Ah, come on.
Just relieve yourself.
Oh, I just noticed.
You actually see a bar for your potion in the top right.
What the hell?
I never noticed that.
Cool.
Fill me up before I go.
There we go.
A bit more.
Now I want to blow that up down there.
Oh, that works too.
Is that gonna burn?
Is it gonna make it?
Oh, nice.
Yes.
It's gonna burn away and the water's gonna go.
Cool.
Saving my bombs.
Good thing the hearts can't get destroyed, huh?
Imagine that.
Man, this is a good start so far.
I found one heart at the top and then one heart here now.
And it hasn't even been like five minutes.
Why is the water not going through here?
Come on.
The hell is happening?
Let me help it along.
There we go.
Much better.
150 HP, baby.
Not bad at all.
Uh, let's go here.
Hold on.
What if I put water in here?
I mean, it's just gonna...
You know what?
Burn the oil!
Because it's so satisfying.
And then it's gonna burn.
Oh, then it's gonna burn through down there and I can get through it, it seems.
Or can I?
It's actually rock.
Never mind.
Shit.
All right, I gotta get back into this.
I've been using a lot of dynamite.
It's not the most... Oh, I could have just walked down here.
Great.
Oh well.
It was fun watching that oil burn.
In fact, it's fun watching most things burn.
Not a pyromaniac.
Just want to put that out there.
What's up, man?
Look at this little peak hole.
Nice.
Who else wants some?
Oh, we've got dudes.
Whoop.
Love that guitar riff.
At least I think it's a guitar.
I actually don't know if it's pronounced guitar or guitar.
In fact, I don't even know how to say it in Danish now when I think about it.
Guitar.
I know how to say it in Danish.
I just had to do it.
Whoa.
Oh, I'm on fire.
See, that's why we carry water, baby.
That's called preparing for the future.
And oh boy, did I prepare.
Let me get up here.
Can I help this fire along somehow?
Wait, am I putting it out by shooting it?
Ah, probably not.
Cool house, little pieces of the wood break off.
That's not gonna...
You know what?
I'm gonna let that do its thing while I go this way.
Oh, I could have just done this.
Wait, what the hell is that?
It's like a little bridge.
Look at that.
Weird.
I don't know why I'm so surprised by that.
Yes, I've just never seen it.
Man, this fire is burning forever.
What's this?
Teleportation.
Damn, that's a lot of it.
What the fuck?
Can I quickly grab this before I get teleported?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm gonna fly somewhere else now, right?
Take me.
Okay.
Nice.
Whoa.
It's a frog.
Kill it.
I have no longer telepor... What is this?
Orbs collected... Oh, I have not even noticed this until now.
I have collected one orb.
I... Uh-huh.
How come I'm just noticing this stuff now?
Weird.
Oh, collapsed mines is here, huh?
We've got a... Is that berserkium?
Don't shoot me.
My god, he has a lot of HP.
Man, that's so well done.
Just the sound of that barrel, too, is perfect, you know?
It's exactly what you would expect.
From a heavy barrel filled with, I guess, oil?
Or something ex... a little explosive.
Who's behind me?
What's going on here?
Hold on, I'm gonna do this.
Blow this up.
Let me in.
Show me the goods.
Aha!
We've got Hamis!
I like Hamis.
Apparently, it's a spider, but that's the one spider I love.
I love Hamis.
Wasn't there an enemy here?
There was.
Can't quite hit him like that.
I need to sort of...
Wait, is that a dead enemy, or... Oh, he's dead.
Oh, okay.
Hamis, and a little acid monster.
Acceleration, I'll take it.
Watch this.
Come here.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, come on.
Okay, let's calm down here.
Sir?
Fucking love it.
That was great.
Exactly what I needed.
Whoa!
A chest!
Oh!
A wand!
Let me see here.
A bunch of triplicate bolts.
Wait a minute, that's the digging one, isn't it?
That digs!
Hold on.
Before I do anything, let me go up here.
This thing can hurt me, no?
Oh, it doesn't shoot.
It doesn't have enough mana, I guess.
90 mana drain on that.
Holy crap.
Wow.
Okay, it does shoot, huh?
Yeah, there's one part it doesn't shoot.
Yeah.
Okay.
There's a wand up there as well, I see it.
Very cool.
I like it.
Kind of want that all-seeing eye spell right now.
Also, is there anything in there?
Why is there so much acid?
There's just stuff below me.
I don't want to use my explosives just yet.
I have three left only.
That was close.
I could go upstairs here.
Wait, how did I lose HP?
Oh wait, I was on fire, right.
I remember now.
I've already been here.
Wait, can I get through here?
No.
Oh actually, I can.
I'm just gonna use this.
Make a little hole here.
Yeah, look at that.
In fact, I'm gonna kill Himus with it.
I'm sorry, Himus.
I love you.
There we go.
There was a tiny pixel that I couldn't get through.
Had to sort of hit it straight on, it seemed.
Okay, is there another Himus?
Hahaha.
Sucker.
Nice.
Let's put out this fire.
Man, putting out fire is actually not as easy as it may think.
Water is not really that...
Ooh.
Okay.
That is a trap.
There's two of them.
So what is that symbol?
Oh, oh, okay, okay.
I understand now.
They actually have separate symbols for things.
Remember when we saw the lightning symbol?
That was electricity.
This is fire symbol.
Pretty cool.
But that's not gonna do anything if I take this.
That's fine.
Oh, wait, this is a sick wand.
Right?
Look at the low recharge time and cast a leg.
Wait, isn't that kind of sick?
Point.
Oh, and it's no shuffle.
Oh, wait, this is, wait, it's this one.
Oh, it does shuffle.
Ah, crap.
But I guess I could put on these things right here and make it really nice.
So maybe I will replace this one.
Yeah.
Oh, wait a minute.
I can use this to dig, no?
Circle of shielding.
I don't really care about that, I don't think.
This is a nice amount of damage though.
Hmm.
No, I'm gonna take this wand.
I can always come back for this if I need to, right?
Chest!
Fuck yeah!
Ah, there we go.
How do I, you know what?
Let me grab this wand.
Real quick, we're gonna use it to dig.
This is the digging wand.
I guess I could also do this.
Oh, never mind, I guess.
I see a haemus.
Oh, I thought I just destroyed it, but we're fine.
What's this?
Luminous drill.
Whoa, look at the cast delay on that.
Point zero?
750 max mana?
Oh, but the mana charge speed.
Eee.
So that's one of those ones you want to just empty real quick and then forget about it for 10 minutes.
Maybe I'll take it?
That could be interesting to play with.
And there's also another one down there, man.
And another one!
Wow!
What the hell is happening?
I'm getting really lucky here.
What is this?
Invisi- Oh my god, look at all the stuff I'm getting.
Invisibilium.
Man, I have blood, acceleration, and invisibilium.
I've got it all.
Can I drink the invisibilium?
No, that's the one I can't drink.
I have to douse myself with it.
I'm puking right now.
That's not very good.
Dude, the triple coat is actually also a great damage dealer.
Hey Barney!
I call him Barney, because he looks like the Barney from Simpsons.
What the hell is that?
Shiny orb?
Wait, wait, wait.
Get rid of blood.
Shiny orb.
It hums slightly.
What happens if you kick it, you wonder?
Yeah, what?
Okay, you know what?
Shiny orb?
We're gonna try something here.
Like I said, we're gonna try things today.
All kinds of things.
We will do experimentation.
Oh man, look at how that one looks.
And a chest!
What is happening?
Oh, 200!
Wow.
Dude, this is sick.
Also, I have a drill now.
That actually kills him.
Cool.
I don't want to drill that though.
I kind of want to do that.
Let me in.
Oh, I could just walk around.
I'm an idiot.
Another wand!
What the hell is... Oh, he has a wand!
Oh, that was close.
Oh, rain cloud.
Hmm.
I don't think I like it.
The stats on the wand is not that great.
Whoa!
A bunch of spark bolts with triggers.
Maybe I do want that.
It's shuffled though.
What?
I can always take those spells later, right?
Oh, you have to be careful.
Sparkly bounce.
Hold on.
Cool.
I mean, not bad.
I think I like it.
Energy sphere.
This is a good wand.
Um, maybe I...
Shit, man.
Replace the first, I guess.
Oh yeah, the sick wand!
Yeah, fuck the first wand I had.
I don't want that anymore.
Also, there's another wand over here.
This is an insane level.
Okay, I don't want that.
Whoa, sir.
I'm walking here.
Hamis.
Oh wait, you're still alive?
Wait, there was two of them, I guess.
Okay, so here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go to the top now, and I'm gonna try this golden sphere that I found.
And hopefully I will be rewarded for my curiosity, if you know what I mean.
How do I get up again?
I guess through here.
I could also jump in here again.
That would be fun.
Later.
We're gonna jump in here later.
In fact, I may take some of this with me.
So I'm gonna try and kick that sphere, of course.
I think I tried it once, and I didn't quite understand what was happening.
All right, here we go.
Bring it to the top.
Sick.
Look at how precise I am with my movement.
I'm a god.
Okay, let's see here.
I offer this
shiny orb.
Gods above, will thou take my shiny orb?
Maybe not.
Hold on, actually.
Eh.
Oh!
Cool!
God damn it.
I feel like that happened once before.
But maybe not in this exact manner.
Something like that happened before.
And I completely forgot about it.
Shit.
Those bastards.
I wonder if I could have just shot it.
I'm gonna try that next time, I guess.
799 gold already.
Dude, we're gonna be rerolling perks so much.
It's gonna be great.
What is up here?
Probably nothing.
Don't go that way.
Hold on, I can just do this.
Let me through.
Man, this is not very efficient, is it?
I mean, it works, but god damn.
That takes a while.
Oh, oh yeah, that's the one I already checked.
What do we have here?
Oh, that's something.
No, never mind.
So I could grab the extra health all the way to the right, spawn the boss, and GTFO.
The problem is, this is a great run, and there's a chance it could fuck me up.
So maybe I don't do that, actually.
Maybe I play the adult tier, the responsible one, and say, don't take the chance.
It's dumb.
You know?
It's not worth it.
Get me out of here.
This is it.
This is that area.
I'm not going over there.
I'm not.
We're playing it safe.
Another one.
This is insanity.
Oh my god.
Hey,
all seeing eye.
Uh, I guess I could use it temporarily.
Just to have some fun.
Oh, I see electricity symbol.
Yeah, let's just walk around with this for a bit and just reveal some stuff.
So I have to remember, this wand here is all the way to the there we go.
Let's take him out.
Which one was this?
Oh, dynamite.
You know what?
No.
Unless I need to do some serious digging.
Okay, nothing that way.
Holy mountain.
See, it's called holy mountain.
Doesn't that kind of make you think of some kind of temple on a mountain with like monks and you have the bells going, you know?
And they're all chanting and stuff.
That's what I think of.
Like, why is it holy mountain?
Is it made in the name of the gods?
Is it for the gods?
Like, what is going on?
Who are the gods?
I guess I killed a god last time.
The gods are angry and someone came after me.
Although that could also not be a god, you know?
It could be just someone that god sent to kill me.
There we go.
Let's see what we got here.
Not much.
Can I?
Okay.
I thought maybe that would, because it's such a violent shot, maybe there would be some explosive power in it.
I should probably get rid of that.
Whoa!
Damn!
Look at all that fire!
Oh, a portal!
Very neat.
Damn, son.
Wow, what an amazing.
Now, do I even?
So, what is it?
Hold on.
What is with the copper?
Let me try and loosen that.
It's just copper falling down.
Okay.
I thought maybe it would be worth something.
It's just pooling down there now.
Let me in!
Yes!
Look at that.
Blow that shit up, because that's a bunch of water.
It doesn't matter.
Okay, you can definitely take out fire with water.
You just need a lot of it.
Blow everything up.
There's, oh, there's people up here.
Let's check that out.
There's a way in up here.
This is steel.
He died from it.
Amazing.
Let me also do that.
Hold on.
So, I have water.
Good.
Invisibilum.
Acceleration.
Okay, okay.
Just reminding myself what I have at my disposal.
Yo, sir.
You almost just killed yourself.
Oh, there's stuff up here too.
What the hell?
I'm exploring this first area so thoroughly.
It's insane.
Whoa, what the hell just happened?
Did my projectile bounce?
I think it did.
Somehow it bounced and it hit those guys.
Can I get in here without?
Okay, there's nothing in here.
Damn it.
Solid.
What's that?
More invisible.
I'll take it.
Nice.
There's actually stuff on that side too.
Hold on.
Wow, that almost sprayed me right in the eye.
Would have been bad.
Order that shit.
In fact, look at how well.
It's slowly being converted.
Like, all of it is actually being converted slowly.
Oh, it's swamp.
Weird.
There's stuff above me.
So, wait, is this the collab?
Whoa!
Damn!
Holy shit, things can go wrong so quick in this game.
That was insane.
What just happened?
Okay, we're playing it mega safe now.
Fuck you!
Burn that acid.
Shit, what's up here?
Nothing.
Okay.
Wait.
Wait, where am I?
Is this the root of the tree?
Dude, that's exactly what it is.
Why is everything so dark here?
What?
It doesn't get revealed.
Oh, I'm scared.
What the hell is this?
Oh, wait, I'm standing on something.
What?
Listen to the music.
Hold on.
Can I enter from the bottom?
Dude, what is that place?
I'm mega intrigued.
Okay, thank God he died.
I sort of put myself on a corner there.
Can I get in here?
Slowly I can.
Can I dig a little better?
Not really.
Drain the water.
If that water goes all the way to the top.
Interesting.
I kind of want to grab my dynamite.
You know what?
Let's explore the rest of this place and look for the dynamite at the same time.
It was somewhere on the right.
I'm gonna get in here.
Wait, why is it not digging anymore?
They're just being casualty right now.
Yeah, blow yourself up.
Full.
There we go.
Easy peasy.
And there's nothing in here.
I mean, I got some money out of it.
So right now I have enough for at least two re-rolls.
In fact, three... No, I have almost four re-rolls.
Would be kind of cool to have that.
Take a bath.
There we go.
Now we're nice and wet.
In fact, hold on.
I should be doing stuff like this.
Because look at the gold there.
This is what I can allow myself to do now because I have this wand here.
Maybe I'm going a little too crazy with it.
There we go.
What is that I'm standing on?
Rusted metal.
Where's that wand?
Also, I had a bunch of other ones in here that I kind of wanted to bring.
This one I want to... Oh, wait a minute.
Where's that... I had a wand with zero castile on it, which was insane.
I need to try and find it.
Because I want to bring that with me.
Is it that one?
No, this is the bomb one, I think.
Yeah.
In fact, I'm going to bring this.
Yes.
Bring that.
And what does that wand?
Rain cloud.
No.
That is not the one I wanted.
Maybe it was over here.
Maybe that one, yeah.
Oh, this is the one.
This is the one.
Um...
Do I want this though?
It's not even that good.
You know?
I don't think I want it.
No.
I mean, the spark thing with the trigger is cool and all.
And that's the end of that sentence.
I have no more to say.
I think I like this more.
The triple kit... Do I actually like this?
I think I do like it, yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Mana charge speed 490 on this one.
That's crazy.
That is an insane wand.
Didn't even notice that before.
That's going to charge so fast, it does like... Wow.
As long as you can keep the total mana usage below the maximum, it's going to recharge so fast, you don't even care.
Look at all that acid.
Oh, it's toxic sludge.
Okay, so there's a difference between acid and toxic sludge.
Toxic sludge is like, yeah, it's not good for you.
Acid is like, fuck no, that... I hate that shit.
You know, it's kind of a difference there.
Wait a minute, where am I going right now?
A frog.
Froggy.
Have fun.
Oh, there's a guy there too.
Sup, dude.
Hold on.
If this connects the way I think...
Okay.
Oh, yeah, actually.
No.
I want to try and empty it and then go in from the top.
That works.
And I get gold out of it too.
Oh, you know, I'm gonna... Oh, dude, I'm gonna leave it down here.
Watch this.
It's like a nice rhythm there.
And now that this one is empty, I can replace it again with something else.
Bro, this does not dig through that.
Is it because it's in water?
Oh, okay.
I need to be down here.
I see.
Oh, I think I know what happened.
Oops, I almost died.
The projectiles lose speed in water.
So when I shot it from the top, they lost so much speed, it didn't penetrate.
Look how much water there's in here.
What the...
Yo, can I drain it even more?
I think that's about the amount of draining I can do here.
No more drainage here.
Let me see from the top now.
And notice how the music changes when I'm here.
This is very intriguing.
Look at the roots.
Ah, water's gone.
I'm scared.
What is this place?
Why is it so dark?
I don't understand.
Take a hole.
I mean, it's draining, I guess.
Maybe I'm a bit too obsessed with this.
Ah, fuck it.
I don't know what's going on.
We're going to try that later when we have something better to explode walls with, I mean.
Okay, so is it time?
Let me find the perfect one before I move on.
Also, let me grab this gold right here.
It's right there.
Ah, let me see.
I don't want this one.
That's a shitty wand.
I'm going to replace that with one of the other ones over here.
Also, give me more water.
Thank you.
Man, I'm feeling greedy now.
I kind of want to go grab that extra heart from the boss area.
I'm not going to do it though.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're staying disciplined.
We try to avoid temptations.
This is... which one was this?
This one is actually not bad.
The stats on it, I mean.
But then, what was this one again?
Maybe I would rather have that?
No.
I think I have what I need here.
Yes, I'm going to experiment with these ones here.
Let's go through the portal.
It's time.
Let's-a-go!
Man, that was a great first level.
I'm not going to take that yet.
What do we have?
Is that teleport?
No, it's returned.
Ah, fuck.
Heavy spread.
Okay, let me see this over here.
Wait, don't- why do we open that?
Stronger heart.
Ooh, that would be nice.
No.
Projectile repulsion sector.
Projectiles that fly into a small sector in front of you get blown away.
Huh, that's new.
I mean, this one could be cool, right?
But I have so much money I can't.
I want to re-roll!
Is that crazy?
This one is great.
Okay, if anything, this is great to get early, right?
So I should actually take it.
I'm taking it.
I'm doing the smart thing here.
The earlier you take that one, the better.
Because it's not a thing that retroactively goes in and does things.
Sea of assets.
The chainsaw I want, because it will actually increase the attack rate.
Slimeball?
No.
Maybe?
If I can put something where it explodes somewhere else and it goes off in a pattern?
I mean, I have so much money.
You know what?
I have so much money.
Bomb?
Sure.
In fact, let's get two bombs.
Return.
I don't want anything else here, I don't think.
Sea of assets?
Why would I want that?
I guess it can work on enemies.
Hold on, let me take this now.
Okay, so let's see here.
I have a bunch of things.
So first of all, let's try this one.
It has a cast delay of 0.0.
What?
Let's try that.
Let me go over here and do it.
Right.
But it has a recharge time.
Yes.
Okay, so it has a recharge time.
But if I...
What is this doing?
A good tool for cutting meat also has some magical properties.
Reduces recharge time by 0.17, right?
I mean, that's not very much.
Let's see how this does.
No, it's not that good there.
But if I go like... Watch this now.
If I do this, this is like what we had, right?
Watch this.
It's a little bit faster, I think.
Is it?
Yeah, it is.
It's definitely faster.
0.17 faster, I guess.
Which is weird because this is 0.23 right now.
Oh, wait a minute.
Ah, these one add cast delay as well.
Right.
That makes sense.
Oh, but then I also have this.
That one removes a bunch of cast delay and recharge time too.
Wait a minute.
Stupid question.
Why?
Okay, why is this not exactly... Why is this not a brrr?
Because look, cast delay is 0.03 right now, right?
Both of these add 0.17.
This one subtracts 0.17.
This one subtracts...
0.17.
So that should be zero recharge time now.
And the cast delay should be below zero with this.
So all... This should... Why is that not a brrr?
Like an infinitely fast...
want?
Whoa.
Why is that doing that?
Why is this not infinitely fast?
I think I'm not understanding how this cast delay works after all.
I don't get that.
So that one makes sense, right?
Because, okay.
Okay, so interesting.
Right now this should have, I guess, what is it?
0.34 seconds of recharge time?
Sorry, wait.
Sorry, 0.34 seconds of cast delay.
And then recharge time is three quarters of a second, right?
That makes sense.
Yeah.
See, that makes total sense.
If we now put this in here, this should simply... Well, I guess we can't compare directly like that.
But if we can...
If I do this now... Wait a minute.
And then do this.
Definitely shoots faster.
And that's because the recharge time has been reduced.
Because cast delay is not an issue here.
This is 0.0.
Okay, then we have this one.
Let me try this one.
Pretty cool.
That's just a little...
Oh, wait a minute.
0.17.
Am I limited by cast delay in this case?
Because look, these are adding cast delays.
This is reducing re... This should be a zero recharge time.
So the thing that's dominating this one is actually cast delay.
Okay.
So if I were to put this... This removes a lot of cast delay.
Wait, what?
Why is that not... Bro, I'm so confused.
It... Huh.
Man, at one point I made this go super quick somehow.
And I think I understood it.
But then I don't, it seems.
I don't understand how this works.
I mean, obviously it's also shuffle.
But it should at some point give me some speed.
No, like, randomly out of all those shots.
There's just no way.
The chances on that are just too low.
Let me try this one then.
If I go here.
So this is also just one spell.
These are all one spell per cast.
Let me see now.
Okay.
I think that's the same.
And that is the same because we are limited by recharge time.
Or no, by cast delay, I guess.
Because these all add cast delay.
Okay.
So if I now add this here, does this do anything in this one?
Shit.
Fuck.
Meatballs.
Hmm.
Is it simply too much mana?
Mana drain one.
Yeah, I don't understand.
I don't get it.
But that's fine.
I'll figure it out.
So now the question is, how do I want to make this?
I definitely want to use my triplicate bolts, I think.
And maybe on a one that shoots a little bit faster.
Maybe that one actually.
Two of these here.
These cost 25 mana.
Pretty cool.
But the recharge time is quite large.
What if I put them here?
0.03.
That's actually really low.
Oh, that's nice.
That's real nice.
Makes a projectile separate into a bundle of five explosive bolts as soon as it moves downwards.
Mana drain 90, though.
That's not good.
I do like how that shoots.
That's pretty good.
Double scatter.
I mean, it's all shuffled, so it doesn't really make sense to put anything else in there, I guess.
Yeah.
Okay.
So that's the first wand.
The next could be something like this.
Nothing special.
Oh, wait.
I have wrong wand.
I think I do want the vision on that one.
And then have some bombs maybe.
Maybe that's what we're gonna go for.
Keep it simple, you know?
Okay.
And with this one, we can actually dig.
Maybe I'll put this in here just to have a random dig.
It's all shuffled, so...
Then again, it does cost mana.
Just 10, though.
No, it's not worth it.
I'll leave it like this, I think.
I could also put it in here somewhere randomly.
Then randomly, this is gonna shoot two extra spells.
Like, in a weird pattern there.
But it does cost a lot of mana.
Does it cost more than usual?
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
Let's keep it like this.
It's like a good start.
Let me buy some more stuff.
Actually, I don't want any of this.
I don't want it.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Actually, I do want to buy the...
That one.
Just to have.
And that one.
I don't like this one particularly much.
Now we can do some digging.
We can do some shooting.
We can do some revealing.
And some... Well, that's it.
That's all we can do.
Let's move on.
Fuck yeah.
This one slaps.
And it's a super good digger too.
Look at that.
Very cool.
Well, not through that material, but you know.
Revealer, activate.
Bum.
Oh shit, I forgot to take the recharger.
Oh, wait, I can still get back, right?
Wait, I can definitely make it.
Oh, this runs out of mana quick though.
So that's something to keep in mind.
In fact, maybe I will keep this one as my primary and then switch it out when I need to do some digging or like heavy damage.
In fact, I just want to make a hole through here so that I can come back here when I need to recharge my stuff.
Because I do want to use up this first and I come back and then I grab it.
Yeah, that's the plan.
That is the plan.
By the way, I wonder.
So last time, for some reason, I think that was a worm.
But there was like, there was a huge tunnel up to the previous area, right?
I thought, I always thought these levels were just like disconnected, you know, instances.
But it seems like it's one whole map because I could physically walk from here to the earlier level.
Which is pretty freaking cool.
So I wonder if I can dig myself back up to the previous level as well, you know.
If I really wanted to.
Could be cool.
Okay.
Give me that gold.
We've got dudes.
You know what?
Let me put this on two because it's more convenient for me.
Damn.
Ha!
Bounced on his head.
Very cool.
Bro!
Damn!
That dude just fucked me up.
Oh, I want to get in there.
Uh, I can do that.
Um, probably the best way is to put a bomb here.
Yeah, I'm gonna do that.
Ha ha.
Yeah, the man on this is a bit of an issue.
Oh!
My dude has aim.
So do I, though.
Fuck you.
He just chopped up his friend.
Fuck yeah.
Beautiful explosion.
Damn, dude.
Uh...
Let me try it.
Whoa!
Wait, why was that so powerful?
Wait a minute.
Weird.
So it shoots the other ones after a timer.
Very weird wand.
Maybe it wanted, actually.
Hmm.
Let me keep the bombs for now.
And then I'll come back for it later.
So I have to remember, it's somewhere in the middle near the beginning.
Middle beginning.
I'll probably forget it.
He just killed himself.
Just fucking shoot them.
There's another one in there.
Fuck!
Drain me!
Why is it so slow?
Oh
my god.
Yeah!
Holy crap!
The poison is killing me right now.
Bombs!
Not a bad wand.
I like the wand.
370 mana max.
But I want to use these bombs for... Let me just...
Whoops, that was not a bomb.
That's okay.
What the hell is going on here?
I have no idea.
Sick.
Bro, this, this, this wand right here is actually amazing.
Damage dealer?
Oh my god.
It can do some damage.
Jesus fucking christ!
Holy...
Oh shit, dude, I'm getting my ass kicked.
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm getting my shit pushed in.
This game is tough.
There's a wand in there.
Barely.
Can I... shit.
Almost.
Yes.
Floating arc and fire bombs.
It's a shuffle though.
I hate shuffle.
Shuffle makes me sad.
What is going on here?
Is... was this a trap of some sort?
What the hell is happening?
Hold on.
Up.
Just blow everything up.
My dude was ready.
Got him.
This is actually a solid run so far.
Don't even think about it, sir.
Who else wants some?
Come on.
Show yourself.
Wait a minute.
This looks very peculiar.
Ah, it's a portal.
Wait, why is that?
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So if you're not entirely resting, it doesn't recharge as much the levitation.
Ooh.
Whoa.
Man, if you're not on your toes at all times in this game, you will get fucked.
That's a wand.
I hate it.
I needed to shoot one shot to know I hated it.
That's all it takes.
Gold for me.
Solid weapon here.
Okay, that's not the... I need something soft to dig through.
The coal is good, like this.
Then I can just go in and take it.
Okay, I have 1100 gold, by the way.
That's because I saved some.
I didn't spend all of it.
All right.
Really should be using that spell more.
It's fantastic.
In fact, I'm gonna use all my charges.
That's my mission.
Use all the charges of the reveal spell.
So I can go back and grab more of it.
Whoa.
Nah, I'm not going through that.
Takes too long, and I'm lazy.
Man, I kind of want to teleport wand.
I have to become addicted to those.
Like, when you get used to the movement with that, it's very hard to go back.
Let me grab some blood.
Man, it smells so much like broccoli.
I think my neighbor is cooking a fucking truckload of broccoli or something.
I don't know.
It's just very broccoli.
It smells good.
But very broccoli smelling.
Don't know what the hell is going on.
Also, why are all my hearts now that I have this perk?
Come on.
Give me the hearts, please.
Whoa, there's a big guy.
Okay, I'm pushing.
Oh, there we go, there we go.
Oh, he's slowly dying.
What's up, bro?
That's right.
Yeah, there we go.
63 HP.
That's not very much, is it?
I'm scared.
Oh, I can't get through.
Oh, it's a wall.
Hello.
How are you not dead?
Wait, am I stuck?
There's a wand there.
Love that spell.
Oh, it's just blood.
Fill me up.
Can't get in there.
You know, if you're smart, you can sort of dig your way through the coal vein all the way.
In a, in a pinch, you know, you could do it.
Like coal there, coal here, coal everywhere.
What, which one was, was this the one I wanted to bring with me?
Yes, it was.
No.
I don't know if I like that.
I don't like the luminous drill with timer.
And it's mostly because I don't quite understand how to utilize it, I think.
Just yet, at least.
In
fact, give me this gold.
Look how easy that was.
I should be doing that.
Whenever I see coal only with some gold, just grab it.
Well, this is too far away.
See, that's pretty close, like borderline, you know?
Look at this!
What the hell is this place?
What is this mechanism?
Holy shit, he's throwing lava.
Holy crap.
What, he just exploded and... I don't even know what that is.
What is this?
Oh, it's the freezing vapor.
Let's wait a bit.
Why does that keep going?
Come on.
Oh, I'm burning!
Shit!
Yo, look at that wheel of fire.
Pretty sweet, honestly.
I like the way that looks.
Okay, I'm gonna burn... I'm gonna blow that up, I think.
Ah, shit!
The one place I can't stand.
I can't stand that place.
Wait, I didn't get that?
So, I've been up there.
Revealed... Oh, I've been here, too.
Oh, I used all my... Ah!
I used all my all-seeing eye.
Shit.
Is that an acid?
Fucking hell.
Oh my god, I didn't see you!
Oh, this is getting a bit... this is getting scary.
Man, oh man.
And that... there's a heart.
I worked so hard to get that.
Mr. Spirits.
Uh, I mean, I like the triple spell.
That's cool.
But I don't like much else, honestly.
Maybe I will...
Hmm.
Okay.
Let me make a bomb here.
That's not a bomb!
I just replaced it, because I'm an idiot.
Ah, that's whatever.
I have found my heart.
I think it's time to get out.
But wait a minute.
What do we have up here?
Dude with a shotgun?
Another dude with a shotgun!
Why am I doing this?
It's a terrible idea.
I should not be doing this.
Why am I doing it?
Okay.
Okay, now, but for reals, we're gonna go.
We're gonna go.
We have money.
We have our life.
Whoops.
Heart!
Whoa, that almost hit me.
Holy crap.
Uh, the best way to get in there is to actually go like this.
Oh my god, that one pixel.
There's a dude in there as well.
This is, uh, a little sketchy.
See if we can't fub.
Okay, okay, okay.
He's coming.
Come here.
Ah, fuck you, man.
Gotcha!
And then we can grab this gold as well while we're at it.
Oh, lovely.
Look at that.
1400 monies in the bank.
I have an idea.
He's gonna blow up.
That's so funny.
He's dead.
Fire's coming.
This thing is drunk.
A big one.
I don't know why I'm doing this.
I'm going back.
We're going back.
No more fucking around.
We're finding the portal.
Hold on.
It's for you!
Let's not go that way.
We're not going that way.
Where is the portal?
Is it down here?
It's not.
Let's go a little further.
Is it somewhere here?
Wait, did I even find the portal?
Oh, shit!
There's a wand though.
Oh my god, I can't hit.
Got him.
Let's see.
Hello!
I like the damage plus.
I do like that.
Maybe I'll take that instead of this one.
Fuck yeah, dude.
That's a sick one.
And here we are.
We're going in.
All right.
I'm gonna heal immediately.
I'm scared.
25 HP scares me.
Glowing lands, baby!
Fuck yeah!
Okay, before we do that, let me check perks.
What's that?
Eat your vegetables.
You inflict more damage the more satiated you are.
Uh, no.
Gas blood.
You, no.
Repelling cape.
Stains drop at a fast rate when moving.
Oh!
Now that could be interesting, but nah.
Boink!
What's this?
Extra item in holy mountain.
There will be an additional item in every holy mountain you haven't discovered yet.
Okay.
Spontaneous generation.
Vomit near you evolves into helpful red minions.
Critical hit plus.
I'm tempted to reroll again.
I'm gonna reroll again.
One more, one more.
Dissolve powders.
Sand and other soft powdery materials dissolve quickly.
Attract gold.
No, that, no.
Peace with gods.
You make peace with your gods.
Wait, can I, I wonder if I can take that now and I will be forever pieced in case I somehow anger the gods?
Hmm.
That wouldn't be too bad.
Uh, I'm tempted to reroll again, but then I won't be able to buy anything.
And I do want this lands.
Oh, there's also this one.
Circle of vigor.
That's the healing.
That's good.
Ooh, 140.
Wait, what is this one?
Magic arrow.
Oh no, I don't have enough.
Wait, I can come back here though.
I can come back.
I can totally come back and buy this later.
Energy orb with a trigger.
Yo, that sounds cool.
There's also spark bolt with a trigger.
Glowing, but glowing lands though.
Oh, but hold on.
If we have, since we have this, that's the one that makes sense to put on something that shoots fast, right?
So spark bolt, for example, or since we already deal with energy bolts or energy spheres, maybe that one.
Oh, but then again, they're not that cool.
You know, they're not as energy bolt-y as you would like.
Spark bolt with a timer.
I definitely need to buy this.
Oh my God, I'm an idiot.
I looked up here.
I thought I had 270 gold.
I'm an idiot, man.
I have 700 gold left.
What the fuck?
I thought I had to choose.
Ah, dude.
What the?
I'm so dumb.
Glowing lands.
Yeah, I'm taking these then.
Oh my God.
I can't believe I just did that.
Uh, what's this?
Long distance cast.
That could, actually that could be useful.
Give me this one as well.
Sure.
Hold on.
I need to remind myself what that is.
And then I think I want this.
Yeah, buy everything.
Just fucking buy everything.
And then we experiment.
We have a bunch of prickly spore pods.
Uh, these are kind of dangerous.
I'm going to put them in the water.
I don't think I want them.
Okay.
Let's see if we have a sick wand.
Oh man.
All of our wands are shuffled wands.
Oh no, dude.
Fuck.
I thought I had at least one that wasn't shuffled.
Oh, I fucked up.
God damn it.
Oh no.
That's, that's, that's, that's not good.
That's terrible.
But I guess I can...
You know what?
We can actually, we can have a solid damaging wand.
Just by doing this.
So what is this one?
Wait a minute.
Huh.
It's green.
This one does 35.
It shoots longer and more accurately.
This one is harder to aim.
That's the thing.
Blowing lands.
35 damage.
That's significant.
We can probably do that a little faster.
Let's see.
Maybe not.
This one is probably also okay for that sort of thing.
I like that.
I do.
It's gonna shuffle everything.
But what if I just put a bunch of bullshit in there?
So that no matter what the shuffle is, it's gonna be decent.
What if I do something like this?
Haha.
That's a mess.
That is a mess.
Obviously.
But I think if I put this in here, it doesn't...
It's just gonna help.
It doesn't matter which direction or which time this happens, right?
Same as that.
Only thing is it's gonna... Oh.
Wait a minute.
Could also use this one.
Just have it somewhere in there.
At some point it's gonna do it, you know?
Let's get these out of here.
Sometimes it shoots too.
That's nice.
I like it.
Just sometimes get a bit of extra damage is what we have, you know?
Gotta work with it.
Could even do this, I guess.
Sometimes they'll have even more damage.
So it's a bit of an RNG.
You can even see when it happens because of the gold.
Now the heal is something we need.
The heal is nice.
And you know what?
We could even do something like...
When we have used all our heal, we can have some fun, you know?
And have more things here.
I don't even know what that would be though.
Hold on.
Oh, it's a projectile modifier.
So it's like the shuffle wands kind of ruin everything.
Honestly, the whole experimenting with wands right now here doesn't make too much sense.
Simply because... Oh, that's different.
Simply because we...
Well, everything shuffles so it makes no sense to experiment too much.
So it is what it is.
I don't want this either.
Maybe I don't want this.
Do I want this?
Maybe I want this.
It's a bit of a mess.
Maybe leave it up here.
Oh, you know what?
Put it here.
It's fine.
Everything's being shuffled into one giant beautiful mess.
Take it out.
I like having this digging wand here.
This is a good one.
Okay, then we have the heal.
And then on this one, we're gonna have the lances.
And on the first one, instead of that, maybe you try that.
It's just randomly gonna shoot something new.
But is that really something good?
I hate that one.
Yeah, I want to put something else here.
Like I would love to put some bombs here, you know?
Maybe Thundercloud.
Static projectile.
Oh, wait a minute.
Ah, but it's all shuffled.
We can't predict what's gonna happen then.
Dang it.
But what if I do this?
Hold on.
If it's shuffle anyway.
Hey, that's not bad.
In fact, what if we just throw this in here so that sometimes we're gonna have a bit of extra damage.
Not bad.
Honestly, I like it.
I like it.
Let's take a perk.
Also, do I have more?
I could add this.
Yeah, that's cool.
That's a decent amount of damage.
I like it.
Ah, okay.
I think I want... Man, I don't like any of these, honestly.
I hope when I take this, it's gonna give me a buff over here that says Peace Forever.
You make... Yeah, okay.
So the fact that this is here, hopefully that means I will not encounter this issue I had.
Oh, let's take the spell refresh.
Before we leave, I have one orb collected.
Wait, what?
One orb.
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So all the hearts I've collected are not orbs.
The orb is the thing I took at the top.
That contained the heart.
So that's different.
Right.
All right.
Yeah, this is... I actually made a little hole here, but I think it's still okay, right?
Yeah, it should be fine.
All right, we're back in this place.
The snowy depths.
Whoa, okay.
We're already starting off here.
That was sick.
Did you see that?
It shot two bolts and they each hit the enemy.
Incredible.
I'm reminiscing about the first time I was here.
I had a weapon like this and it was glorious.
I was sniping left and right.
Good times.
So long range, I'm just gonna use that, you know.
Oh, that runs out of mana fast.
Just wait a bit.
Can I get rid of that little... Okay, nice, I can.
I don't have my seeing eye, unfortunately.
Whoa, what the hell?
Whoa.
Whoa, what a shot.
There's a sniper down there.
Kind of want to take care of him.
Oh, there he is.
Motherfucker right here.
Wait, that's not the thing I wanted.
This is the one I want.
Wait, what?
I wish I could take his weapon and shoot the sniper myself.
I'm not being very systematic in my exploration here.
It's a decent weapon.
Like it's not great, but it's like acceptable at long range.
Wait, what is that?
Oh, it's a rat.
I thought it was a snake with a red head.
That was so weird.
Whoa, my god.
Look at this.
Isn't that cool?
The way the ice broke.
Oh wait, this is wrong wand again.
I keep equipping the wrong wand.
I want my lance.
I'm a lancer.
Okay.
I do actually have Invisiblium.
And that is the one I can't drink.
Right?
Yeah, I have to do that.
Now I could just run around a bit and mess with people.
Whoa, what's happening here?
Oh, shit.
Dude.
My god.
There we go.
What's this?
Oh, whoa.
That doesn't look too bad.
Except it is.
It has like a long recharge.
I think I like this one better.
What is up with these shovel wands?
How about you give me something that isn't shoveled?
Unreal.
Yeah, I want that one.
What's this?
Nothing.
All right.
Where should I go now?
Whoops.
Accidentally kicked my mouse away.
Whoa, look at all this.
Whoa.
Is that a gas pipe?
It's raining.
Yo, that was cool.
That was pretty badass.
Look at the way the cracks spread.
It's so beautiful.
I made a bridge.
Whoa.
Sir.
Where are you?
Dude, he is far.
You did not even die from that.
Insane.
Oh, not these things.
Sir, stop that.
Okay, so this doesn't do too much damage to that one.
What if I use this?
That does nothing.
This is the best I have.
Whoa, whoa.
Look at all the gold falling down on me.
That's the best thing I've ever seen.
Like, look at this shit.
How is that not... Dude, this game is, like, innovative as fuck.
Am I crazy?
Or have I just not played enough games?
Maybe I'm the only one appreciating this shit right here with, like, how they... This is insane.
That is so cool.
I could watch that all day.
Uh, you?
Thank you.
Uh-oh.
What was that?
That looked like a missile.
Jesus!
It's instant.
All right.
I'm finding an alternate path.
Holy shit.
Okay, you want to play?
That's for you.
Shit, I missed this.
He's up there somewhere.
Look at that huge one.
What the fuck?
Why is it so big?
Oh my, it's instant.
How do I get to that?
Okay, I have an idea, I have an idea.
I know how to deal with this guy.
Watch.
Oh, make me invisible.
Oh, I'm wet.
Ah, fuck, okay.
There we go.
Where are you, motherfucker?
Where the fuck is he?
I'm losing my mind.
He's down here.
Is that him?
What's this?
Enlightening bolt?
Triple spell?
Add mana?
Cluster bolt?
Holy shit.
I think I want it.
Oh, it is that guy.
At least I know that now.
Fuck you.
Damn.
That was very unpleasant to deal with.
What's happening here?
Nice portal.
Want to play like that?
Where are you?
Come on.
That wasn't even him.
This guy's a ninja.
Fucking headshot right in the eye.
Right in the medulla.
What's up there?
Oh, oh, it's up.
Whoops.
Oh, well, it didn't mean to do that.
That was actually hilarious.
The platform broke off and I fell into here.
Propane tank?
What?
I get to shoot propane tanks?
Delayed spell cast?
Dude, I don't have enough money for any of this now because of the early entrance.
Plasma cutter.
I'm intrigued by that.
I'm intrigued by plasma cutter.
Hold on.
What's this?
All you can see everywhere.
That would be cool.
No.
Oh, man.
I like this one.
I think that's probably the best.
Although all seeing see all seeing eyes an issue for me because that just makes me lost.
I mean, obviously it's it's a good thing to have an all seeing eye.
But then I'm just fucking lost because I don't know where I've been and where I haven't been.
So that's actually a deep up for me specifically.
I will take the plasma cutter.
Oh, wait a minute.
Let me see.
I guess I could come back later.
Right.
And purchase more.
Circle of fervor.
What is that?
Oh, you know what?
That looks like the berserkium symbol.
Maybe if I stay inside of this, I always crit.
That's my guess.
Avoiding arc.
Propane tank sounds intriguing, honestly, but I'm gonna take this because the only thing I can afford really.
Why does the light cost 280?
It's way too much money.
Oh, but look at this.
We have a non shuffle want now.
That's a great change.
So maybe we can actually do something.
Let me throw away.
I don't want this or that or this or that or this.
We want this maybe.
Clean slate.
This one is cool.
I like this one a lot.
I could replicate my sniper with the projectile thing I had.
No, I don't know yet.
I'm gonna think on it.
I don't like this at all.
This is a horizontal path forces a projectile on a horizontal path, but increases its damage.
Okay.
No, don't want it.
I forgot I had this, by the way.
I should have used that before.
Ah, whatever.
Let's do... I have lightning bolts.
That's a solid one right there, isn't it?
But now I want to play with this one.
And what else do I want to play with?
Add mana maybe.
And maybe let's try this.
Let's try the plasma cutter.
Shit.
Wrong wand.
Good thing I didn't take the spell recharge.
Not bad.
It it cuts very slowly though.
Hmm.
I mean... Oh, oh, no, no.
I need three of them then.
But I guess it does cut through this, which is kind of rare, isn't it?
Oh, hold on.
I think I want this one.
It's like the only sensible choice there for me.
Slow some projectiles down.
Sounds good.
Okay.
What I can do is this.
So this is gonna cast three spells.
That one, that one, and maybe that one.
Let me see.
Oh, let's remove this.
So that's gonna cast three spells.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Is this field affecting my own projectiles?
I feel like there's a bigger arc on these glowing lances than usual.
Fuck.
I think there is.
That's not normal.
Right?
Crap.
Uh, hmm.
I wish I had more just spark bolts and stuff.
I should have taken some of those with me.
You know what?
I'm gonna grab some of these energy spheres.
Oh, I didn't mean to take that.
Fuck.
Uh, wait a minute.
Put this stuff here for now.
I want this.
Maybe I can make something cool out of that.
So if I... Oh, wait.
Whoa.
I have two of these.
So I can make some crazy stuff happen.
So this is gonna cast three spells, right?
The first of those is this one, which contains all these three.
And then it has two more to cast after that.
So what if I... I don't even know.
Let's try this.
Right.
So this shoots all these three and these two at the same time.
So it works exactly like I thought.
If I do this now,
then it shoots three spells.
One, two, three.
But there is no three, so it starts over.
So if I now do... Let's do this, actually.
Just to have a buffer, I guess, or a filler.
Then it's gonna shoot one, two, three.
But there's nothing here, so it's gonna wrap around and grab that again.
Yep.
So wait a minute.
Can I buffer?
Can I just... Oh, dude, it's buffering time.
Buffer!
Well, this doesn't count as a spell, though, does it?
Oh, wait.
Even better.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Even better, even better.
Watch.
So let me look at the board.
It shoots that.
But then sometimes... Oh, okay, okay.
It's because I'm low on mana.
Then it reverts to... Okay.
See, this is the standard when I have enough mana.
But then it does that.
So if I add and add mana now... I guess... there?
It is being added every time.
Is it better?
Let me try and pay attention.
Oh, yeah, definitely is.
I go way quicker now.
So if I add this here...
This is being added every time.
Nice.
Now, if I now do...
What if I...
Hold on.
What else?
I'm trying to look for some filler spell.
I guess this one could be a filler spell.
Let me see.
It does... This is a modifier.
So that modifies this one.
Right?
Which is a multicast.
Yeah.
What I'm trying to do, basically, is see if I can't use this twice.
You know, because of the wrap.
If I can wrap it somehow to abuse the fact that add mana can be used twice somehow.
Maybe if I use... Oh, what is the thing I could use?
Also, I definitely want to use this, by the way.
So these are going to modify all that comes after, right?
This modifier... No, it's going to modify the next projectile, right?
Or the next spell.
And the next spell is the triple spell, which contains all these three.
But what if I now, if one of those triple spells is another triple spell?
containing one of these, that one, and that.
What then?
That's sick.
That's some firework right there.
Holy shit.
Oh, wait a minute.
We can do better, I think.
So three, triple.
One, two, three.
We find out, dude, that.
Interesting.
What a minute.
Something happening there in between.
Look.
Am I crazy?
There's some...
Wait a minute, why is it doing that?
I understand why it's doing that.
So listen, this is what's happening.
It's shooting off all these first, in this exact sequence.
But then because there's a spark bolt with trigger here, this one is a, when this one hits somewhere, it's going to fire off the next spell.
What is the next spell?
It's the damage plus.
So that's why it's going to show this at the front.
You see that?
But very briefly, right here you can see that the damage is being added first.
The very first time.
It's so brief.
But then the next sequence actually starts with the spark bolt there.
Yeah.
All right.
That was just a sanity check.
So what if I now do this instead?
Can I double use that somehow?
No, I think I definitely, if anything, I want to double use the mana, right?
Oh wait, but is it being, is it being used?
Wait a minute.
I'm confusing myself right now.
Wait, I also have this one.
Dude.
Dude, why is it so much fun to do this?
I love just sitting here trying these things.
So this, let me just remind myself.
Right.
And the reason it's so slow is because it's using three, one, two, three, one, two, and there's nothing.
So we need a filler.
That's exactly what's happening.
So this is the big change.
But the problem is our mana.
The problem is the mana.
So if I change these around,
did that add more or less?
Wait a minute.
That's about the same, isn't it?
Yeah, it's about the same.
But if I, oh, let's say I do this actually, put the mana here.
Oh, that's interesting.
Right.
Okay.
Huh.
I kind of like the idea of a triple inside a triple.
Maybe it's a bit crazy.
What if I just remove that and remove that?
Let's just do this.
What happens then?
It's not as quick, obviously.
So it goes one, two, oh wait, then I don't need this.
Then I need to do that.
Oh, but then it's super slow.
The reason is, what is the reason?
It goes three spells.
One, two, three.
Oh, because it just ends the sequence.
So really, I need to be doing, uh, no, no, no, actually, wait a minute.
What if I simply do that?
Okay, three there.
Dude, you know what's crazy about this?
You can have something that looks reasonable, right?
And then you make a small change and things are completely different.
That's what's fucking with me right now.
You know?
I mean, I made something great before.
I did this, that, that, and then I think I filled it like that.
Had that there and this there.
This is the one.
Yeah, that's sick.
Honestly, that's sick.
I like it.
I like that.
That's actually crazy.
That's one of them.
That's going to be one of the ones.
And then our next one, I definitely want to use the lightning.
We gotta have the lightning.
The lightning is too fucking good.
Wait, I also have this one.
Wait a minute.
Right.
Whoa.
Wait, is that better?
Oh wait, I should, I should check over here.
If I'm, if I'm close quarter, that's a lot of damage.
But if I now do this instead,
that's actually better.
Huh.
I guess because these energy spheres here are actually insane.
Oh, wait a minute.
The damage plus.
Let's see.
Let's see if I understand this.
The damage plus affects this spell right here only.
And this is a triple.
So that this is that one, that one, and this one, which contains all these three.
So the damage plus is actually affecting everything.
At least that's how I understand that.
What if I add some crazy, what if I add this to it?
I don't understand what just happened.
Uh, wait a minute.
See, why did that happen?
That's the thing, you know, you make a small change and then suddenly all hell breaks loose.
Okay, so that shoots is everywhere.
Why is it not shooting everywhere when I put it at the end?
Look how it's, oh wait, let me, let me check the board.
I shoot once, shoot twice, three, four.
Ah, wait, when I run out of mana, then something happens.
When I run out of mana, we get that.
Interesting.
So if I can find a way to not run out of mana, let's try to understand this.
Why is this heavy spread not affecting that part?
It's obviously not affecting anything there, but it is affecting the stats, reducing cast delay and recharge time.
But the spread is not being applied.
So heavy spread gives the projectile a much lower cast delay, but no respect to your aim.
Okay, so it's a modifier, right?
What does it modify?
It modifies the next spell.
And the next spell, let's try to understand this.
So this is the spell.
One, two, three.
One of them is a triple.
This is gonna, oh, wait.
Wait, I think I understand.
The spark bolt with trigger, it hits, it collides with something, right?
What happens then?
It shoots off the next spell.
What is the next spell?
It's not this one, because this is a modifier.
So it goes to the front again.
It's not this one, still a modifier, still a modifier.
It's this one.
So it's, so it's only the first salve.
No, wait.
If I just do this, yeah, as soon as my mana is low.
Okay, hmm.
Then I don't quite understand.
Let me just change something.
Okay, that's crazy.
That's nice.
That's shitty.
This is wild, man.
And if I put this in the front, all health breaks loose, right?
Okay, you know what?
I'm just gonna leave this as it is, because I kind of like it.
I mean, it's, maybe I don't like it actually.
The fact that it goes like that at the end.
This is better.
I'm gonna keep it like that.
Later on when I find more mana, hopefully I will find more mana, then I can try and experiment with that.
The second one is gonna be my lightning bolt, so that's just gonna be like, really nice.
I like it.
Then we have our healing.
I like that too.
I kind of want to use my plasma cutter.
What if we disregard the glowing lands?
I know it sounds crazy.
I know it sounds crazy, but oh.
Wait a minute.
Wait, what's happening now?
Is that better?
It's a little less accurate.
Okay.
No, I don't want it then.
Don't want that.
Put that there.
Let's throw away some spells that I absolutely don't want.
I don't think I want horizontal path.
Fire trail.
Yeah, me, me.
Spark bolt.
I could replace one of these.
Nah.
Long distance cast.
We could have a sniper spark bolt or lightning bolt.
Oh wait, that's that.
Oh, it's shuffle.
Dang it.
Fucking shuffles.
Keep messing with me.
So this is good.
The last one, I think I just want to make it into a driller.
Mike, look at that.
It's pretty dope.
Except I don't know if I like that one.
Plasma cutter is cool.
Uh, is there anything else?
Maybe I just want to... I know it's shuffle, but sometimes it starts the center.
I mean, you can use it to dig more, I guess.
It's infinite.
What if I do that?
Yeah, as expected.
I like what I have here.
The only thing I don't like is the energy spheres.
I wish I could replace these with some simple spark bolts.
If that, if I had that, life would be great.
But I don't.
This is sick.
Let's move on.
And let's be, let's remember the second one is electricity.
So don't go in water with that.
That's like the... Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Put this here.
There we go.
Let's go, baby.
We're at the Heezy base now.
Uh, time to shoot some fools.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Damn.
All right, all right, all right.
Up.
Doink.
Man, look how big this wall is.
It's like bigger than my character.
Sure.
It's nuts.
All right, let's fuck up some nerds.
It's not that great at long, right?
Long distance here.
Sir.
Close distance, though.
It's a murderer.
You want to try and hit me?
Wow,
that guy died.
This thing, this thing exploded.
Not bad.
I like my wand.
It's not ideal, but it does the job.
And look at this.
Oh, man, that's actually sick.
Whoa.
Okay, don't go into plasma.
Plasma's bad.
I'm glad I learned that early.
God damn, that could have been a disaster later on.
Yeah, let it do its job and then go in.
Sheesh.
Can I kill them with this?
Uh, sir.
Ooh, sick.
Sir, sir, sir, sir, sir, sir.
I'm stuck, I'm
stuck.
Fuck yeah, everything's gonna blow.
I love it.
Fuck.
Okay, that plasma's gonna kill me.
Look at the physics.
Ah, it's beautiful.
Fuck yo, thingies.
This thing is dangerous.
So these are... what were they called?
Uh, oh, shit, I'm stuck.
Uh, propane tanks.
Propane tanks.
Damn.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
I'm gonna go this way now.
Watch this.
Ooh, cool.
Okay, it doesn't do that much.
But the fact that this can cut through steel like that is actually big.
That's probably the biggest thing about this.
Ah, look at that.
And I can just plasma my way in there.
It even destroys the bed.
How lovely is that?
Fuck yeah.
330, baby.
Sup, nerds?
Want to dance?
Oh, he died.
He died in the freezing vapor.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look, that's actually so cool.
Look at him.
He's gonna die now.
Maybe.
Whoa.
That's a sniper dude.
That's a bomb dude.
It's Barney.
Actually, it's not.
Oh!
I have to remember, I have healing.
I can heal if I need to.
Actually, a big deal.
I should be doing this a bit more.
Yeah, man.
God, the electricity thing here is actually wild.
I could release the acid.
Release the acid!
I don't know why I'm doing it.
Don't ask me why.
Okay.
Boom!
Plasma cutter?
Insane.
I used to not cutting through that little piece.
That's annoying me.
I missed a spot.
Jesus.
Okay, never use it when you're floating.
New rule.
Never plasma while in the air.
Release the acid.
I feel like there's something in there.
I tend to hide things in these little vats of acid and stuff, you know?
It's toxic sludge.
Never mind.
It's not acid.
It could have been.
Oh, you know what?
I have a plasma cutter.
I could just do stuff like this.
Jesus!
I hit myself again with it.
This is becoming a meme.
It's all becoming water.
In fact, it's frozen now.
I wish I had the oil all revealing eye right now.
I'm gonna give up on that one.
He almost just shot his friend.
Whoa!
Oh, shit!
That was almost really bad.
Holy shizan.
Man, what a mess.
This looks like hell itself.
I think it's time to heal.
Let's see how much it heals.
I'm at 151 now and my max is 330.
Okay, not bad.
About 150, something like that.
It's decent.
Boink!
I should not play with these that much.
They're dangerous.
They're so fun.
Off you go.
We blow all that up.
I have to say, this may be my favorite level.
I fucking love the looks of this level, the feeling of it, everything.
I love the enemies.
It's cool.
Lots of explosions.
It's fun, man.
Plasma on my way through.
I have gained entrance to your secret base.
Man, those propane tanks, when they fly around, it's actually one of the scariest things ever.
That's one of my big fears in real life, you know, to have one of those wild tanks.
That guy had a wand!
Holy crap.
I'm playing this ultra save right now.
Look at these wands here.
I'm scared.
I don't know what's on those wands.
And if the enemy has them, makes it even more scary.
Please, please die.
There we go.
What do we got here?
A bunch of giga disc projectiles.
These are scary.
These are the ones that can kill you.
I have experience with that.
Chaotic path, curse, causes a projectile to chaotically fly wherever it wishes.
This wand right here is death itself.
You don't want this wand.
You don't want that, trust me.
That's bad.
Is that a missile?
It is.
Triple scatter.
Dude, 1400 mana?
33.
Holy shit.
Okay, it doesn't recharge fast, but it damn shoots fast.
Could be cool.
Multicast.
It's just gonna shoot a projectile.
I mean, a missile.
50 damage?
It's not even that much.
I don't like it.
Don't like it.
I am tempted to take this one down here, actually, just for the giga discs.
Because they are kind of fun.
Just to make a wand with it later, you know?
I haven't decided yet.
But it seems like the type of weapon that, if used right, I mean, look at it.
63 damage, slice.
And if I can have like a multicast and just fucking shoot them off in a direction, that would be insane.
That would be so much damage.
And the fact that they slice through enemies?
Holy crap, right?
I definitely want to make a wand like that.
If I find some stuff that makes sense with that in here, I'm gonna try and make one.
Damn.
That hurt.
Holy shit.
I just got blown the fuck up.
I got sent into the wall on the left there.
Cool.
Uh, this one again.
Fucking no.
I mean, it is 200 damage, I guess.
I guess.
It has a very low... Oh, this is actually a sick wand.
Dude, look at this.
No, oh, it's only two slots though.
That sucks.
Nah.
Skip.
Hold on, I can just go through here.
Fuck!
That scared me.
I'm starting to hate this plasma cutter.
I'm just standing.
I'm not doing anything and it's still hitting me.
Like, I gotta be so careful with this thing.
It's wild.
Fuck.
I need to heal again, actually.
I need to heal.
Heal me up.
Wait, it heals more the more I move around, it seems.
That just got a little bit scary there.
Fuck you, dude.
Why did I just take damage?
If I shoot it above me, it's fine.
Above is good.
Below is bad.
And that was the last heal I had, so...
What are you shooting at, sir?
That was evil and I love it.
You like plasma cutters?
Me too.
Come on.
Man, this wand is sick.
Ow!
Watch this.
Boink!
And everything dies.
It's that simple.
You just hit them with a bit of a spark and poof, they go organs everywhere.
Lovely.
You want some of this?
Oh, the DPS, man.
Not to be traveled with.
Look at all these explosives over here.
Seems like a bit of a hazard, doesn't it?
Oh my god, die, please!
Jesus.
Good thing he didn't do too much damage there.
All right.
Man, I think this force field is really helping me.
Sweet.
I love this level.
This is so much fun.
Then we have... what's that?
Earthquake shot.
Makes a projectile crumble the earth it hits?
What?
I gotta try that immediately.
Uh, try this one.
Boop!
Where's the quaking?
Oh, wait, it's shuffle, isn't it?
Okay, it's shuffle, so it's not actually guaranteed.
Uh, okay.
Shit!
I was stuck there.
I don't want it.
Change it back.
Oh, there's a guy there.
So the way I'm gonna do this from now on, when I dig down, I'm gonna jump and then move away like that.
That's the safe way to do it.
Look at that.
Smooth.
Whee!
I'm on fire.
Good thing we have water.
We actually don't have any water left around.
I used the remaining.
Time to look for some more.
Give me a bit here.
Thank you.
Oh, nice!
Yank!
You know, it would make sense to put a little light on some of these ones just to light up areas, you know, when you shoot.
I'm thinking about that dark area in the snowy depths.
Oh, hello!
What's this?
Just blood?
I can purchase blood.
Look at this little hut here in the, in a cave.
Magic bolts.
Oh, I don't know.
Delayed?
I'm gonna try delayed spell cat.
I don't know what that is.
Um, I think I want to get rid of...
Maybe I'll get rid of this.
Oh, there's a guy coming.
There we go.
I kind of want to try blood.
Blood, blood, blood.
Fuck these fish.
Secrets?
All right.
We're going to try blood, blood, blood.
At the next holy mountain.
Hello.
Wow, you are not dead.
Oh, shit.
I don't have water.
Okay.
Yeah, we gotta, we gotta get some water.
Right here.
Water.
Oh, no, it's freezing.
Water's freezing on me.
There we go.
I got some water.
It's enough to put out at least one fire.
Grab some more.
Watch this.
This is how you blow it up.
Oh, almost.
He's gonna die.
Oh, he's not.
Motherfucker.
Hey.
Haha.
Bitch.
Don't mess with me.
Don't mess with me, bruh.
Caught through that ice or snow.
Surprise, motherfucker.
What's in here?
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Oh, it's this place again.
Oh, fuck.
I just hit myself again.
There's gotta be something about this place.
I don't know what I'm trying to do.
I kind of want to sacrifice something on top of this.
So, that's the portal.
Don't want to go in just yet.
I have more I want to do.
And when I say that, what I really mean is I have more enemies I want to murder.
My bloodlust is not satiated yet.
Where'd the other guy go?
Did I kill him?
No, he's there.
No, wait.
That wasn't it.
There was a sniper somewhere.
I think there were two snipers.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Wand!
Sweet.
Holy shit.
Another ad mana?
I need that.
Larpa explosion.
Will shoot out eight copies of itself when it expires or hits the ground.
Holy crap.
Dormant crystal.
A crystal that explodes when caught in an explosion.
Okay.
Large fire bolts and a bunch of shit.
You know what?
I think I want this.
Oh man.
Oh, that's a toughie.
What do I... I guess I could remove this one.
Ah, damn.
This is a hard choice.
I really want this wand.
Uh, god damn it.
Hold on.
Is there a way I can do this?
I can get rid of the plasma.
I can live without the plasma.
I'm gonna live without the plasma.
If I need plasma, I'm gonna come back here.
It's sad.
Goodbye plasma.
You were great.
You were so great.
And I will see you again in the future.
But it's just not in the stars right now.
I have other plans.
I need some mana up this wand, you know.
Another wand.
Wait, did I try that on already?
I've been here for sure.
Oh yes, that one.
Why is it still glowing then?
Maybe they just do that.
I guess they stop...
I thought they stopped glowing when I approached it or something.
See, now I would have loved my plasma cutter here.
Can I get through some other way?
Oh, that just sets it.
Okay, that's not good.
You know what?
Maybe I'll pick this one up when I'm done here.
That probably makes more sense.
I'm gonna pick up this wand on the way out of here.
That's the new plan.
Wait, where was it again?
What?
Where the hell?
Was it here?
It was definitely to the east.
Then I went up here.
Yeah, yeah, this is it.
Then I went like that.
And it's somewhere in here.
Down this way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is it.
Is it though?
I don't know if it is.
I don't think it is.
Fuck!
No!
I'm lost.
How is it possible?
I just left it.
This whole fucking place looks the same.
Is it that one?
It's... Oh, fuck!
Whatever!
Plasma cutter, it was good knowing you.
I'll see you when I see you.
Which is never... Oh, it's that one.
It's that one.
That's so hidden though.
Look at that.
That's hard to see.
That's hard to spot.
How do I even get in there?
God damn it.
I think I made a hole down here.
I didn't.
Fuck.
This is unreal.
All right.
Now it's just out of spite.
I don't want the plasma cutter anymore.
Out of spite.
Fuck you, plasma cutter.
Missile.
Oh, this one, right.
Kind of wanted that.
Let's see what we got here.
Damn, is there another better way of doing that?
Okay, that works.
Yeah.
Man, the plasma cutter is actually... Wow, it's handy to be able to dig.
When you've tasted the sweetness of the dig, it's hard to go back, you know?
That sentence just sounded very wrong.
I realize.
I swear I didn't mean to sound like that.
It just happened.
What is this place?
It's a bar.
Look, they're serving drinks.
It's a club.
I like these easy boys.
Heart.
Hello.
This is awkward.
Oh, okay.
Fuck you.
All that oil.
You know what?
I don't want that money.
It's not worth it.
Oh, but I do want this heart.
I need the plasma cutter.
I need to find out where it is.
I simply need it.
It's so stupid.
I don't know where the fuck it is.
New
rule from now on.
Never replace the plasma cutter.
No matter what.
Definitely to the right.
So let's go through this place with a fine comb.
Where could it be?
This one was the box, wasn't it?
Yes.
The exploding box.
It wasn't down there because I haven't been there.
Let's be on the lookout for a wand just lying on the floor.
That's blood.
Wait a minute.
Nope.
It's obviously a path that I could have taken.
So this is not it.
It's got to be through here.
And maybe I'll replace my lightning.
It is sweet, but I like this wand a lot, actually.
It's really growing on me.
I think I went through here.
This sparks a memory in me.
Is the wand somewhere here?
It doesn't look like it.
It's insane how lost I am.
Like, this whole place looks identical.
Did I change it in here?
I didn't.
Is it that one?
That may be it, actually.
Is it somewhere?
Bro, I have no idea where the fuck that wand is!
Driving me nuts!
Come here.
Whoa!
Jesus!
Fire me.
I mean, water me.
Don't fire me.
I don't want to lose my job.
Like,
I don't understand.
I've checked everywhere.
I didn't go far.
Maybe it was all the way up.
This is such a classic moment.
I hate it.
It's not that one.
I checked that one already.
But is it somewhere else up here?
Is this lead somewhere?
Wait, is it that one?
It is that one.
What?
Didn't I check that before?
I could have sworn that wasn't it.
But okay, here we go.
I found it.
We're back.
That was tough.
That was a challenge.
I got it.
Everything's fine.
He says while everything's burning.
Classic meme.
Why is it still burning, by the way?
Shouldn't it stop at some point?
Okay, so here's the bar.
There should be a heart.
Come on, close by.
Sir.
There it is.
Give me that.
Oh, there's another heart.
Fuck yeah.
Oh, sweet.
My patience rewards me.
Skip it up.
Nice.
It just fell into my head.
It's my head.
I want to get through here.
Oh, I totally...
What do you call it?
Boil the water.
Oh, you know what?
I actually need more water.
Pick it up.
Good.
Oh,
it feels good to have this thing again.
I don't know what went through me.
Why would I ever get rid of it?
What?
He shot himself.
I think.
Oh, you know what?
Check this.
It's going to turn into water.
Just a bit more.
Haha.
What a slaughter.
Jesus Christ.
There's so many.
600 gold now.
I feel like that's not even that much.
But I guess I did spend some in here already.
Oh, almost got some ice in my head.
I don't know if that's bad.
What's up, guys?
The good thing about this level is lots of enemies to kill and get money from.
It's big, so there's lots to explore and it's relatively easy too.
So this is just a joy, you know?
It's like the perfect difficulty level.
It's really fun.
Headshot.
Give me that.
Is there a secret here?
Probably not.
I see you there, sir.
But you're on the other side of that, okay.
Hahaha.
Absolutely love the kick and shoot combo.
That is flammoxium.
Okay.
Flammoxium.
There's a guy there.
That's Barney.
You had enough, Barney?
Why is that thing on top of that?
I don't like it.
Hey.
Hahaha.
That was so violent.
His head was stuck in the ice and then he was decapitated and his rest of his body fell down and I was showered in his blood.
That's how this game works, man.
Great.
Oh, you know what?
Can I go through this?
Dude, I know what I want to do.
I know what... Oh wait, do I need to go to snowy depths for that?
Remember we discovered a thing inside the wall somewhere?
On the way up to the boss.
I can get in there now.
But I think that may have been in snowy depths or was it all the way to the east here?
I gotta...
But I've already been to the east in this level.
I think it was snowy depths.
Uh, come here.
Oops.
Oh wait.
See, all this acid makes me think there's stuff in here.
So release the acid.
In fact, can I just burn away the acid with the plasma?
Hell yeah, I can.
It's all getting turned into water.
I guess there was a little bit of water in here.
I keep saying as I mean, toxic sludge, of course.
I see you there.
Whoa.
That was a violent explosion.
All right, there's nothing in here.
That's unfortunate.
I kind of want to go through here.
Wow, that doesn't do anything in water.
Okay.
Lesson learned.
I understand.
I get it.
Oh wait, I can just go like this.
Man, the freezing ice is messing with me.
Boink.
Down with it.
No.
Oh my God.
Come on.
I got buried in the snow.
Oh shit.
There's a bunch of people there.
What's up guys?
Ho.
Man, I am just messing up their base.
They are not having a good day here.
Ha ha ha.
I'm losing a bit too much HP.
Also, I'm in oil and it's burning.
Bad combo.
Dude, I kind of just want to... How about we just make a tunnel?
I'm actually too curious here.
Dude, I can go back up to snowy depths using this.
Yo.
Okay.
First things first.
Let's try this.
Come on.
Ow.
It's because I was oily.
I was so slippery.
Oh my God.
I'm getting that feeling where I have to take a shit, because I'm doing something I'm not allowed to in the game.
I told you about this already.
This is this type of moment that would induce it.
And it is doing it.
It's happening.
Oh.
What?
How do I get hit there?
I don't understand.
Okay.
From now on, we walk away from it no matter where we stand.
Wait for it to do it.
I'm so scared of this plasma.
It's wild.
Okay.
Why is it not burning that little piece in front of me?
There we go.
Oh, fuck.
Dude.
All right.
No.
I'm going to kill myself.
I'm going to kill myself doing this.
This is just stupid.
I'm, I'm being a total maniac.
I should not be let anywhere near laser cutters or plasmas or anything like that.
Lasers.
Nope.
I do not have the certification to operate these machineries.
I shot their land.
Okay.
The plan is to get like a thousand gold and then we go on.
Come on.
That's too much fire.
Oh, that looks fine now.
And now it's water.
Bye-bye.
What is that?
Levitation.
I'm going to go this way.
Oh, nice.
Good thing.
I went this way, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, that's the portal, isn't it?
It sure is.
I'm levitating so hard.
Oh, I'm almost dead.
Is this a sign?
I'm burning now.
Okay.
It's a sign.
We got to go.
We got to I'm going.
I'm going.
I'm done.
Immediately take the healing.
500 HP.
Damn.
That's crazy.
What do we got?
Uh, there's nothing really I want.
I mean, I guess I could take this one is.
Oh, I don't have space.
Okay, fine.
Uh, let's get rid of.
I don't think I like this, but I'm not sure if I like it, so I'm going to keep it.
I don't like this.
I don't like that.
I don't like that either.
This one seems interesting.
A static magical phenomenon that casts three extra spells after a short while.
Okay.
But we, oh, oh, it was of this one.
Fuck.
I forgot about that.
Hey, add mana.
Let's go.
Let's see how much better we can make this.
Let's try this now.
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
It keeps going, baby.
Oh, that's glorious.
What a glorious day it is.
And then we have dormant crystals.
Cool.
Uh, this one trains 150 mana.
Damn.
That's a lot.
That is a lot.
What if I replace one of these?
Huh.
I mean, it costs way less mana.
And wait.
So it's a modifier, right?
Let's just try this.
It's probably crazy.
Okay.
And you know what the funny part is?
It's the energy sphere that's triggering this, because those are the ones going down.
They arc like this, right?
And as soon as they go down, it triggers that one into five explosive bolts.
How much damage does that do?
That's a decent amount of damage.
That's crazy.
Okay.
So I don't even need the extra mana then, I guess, right now.
Oh, I do.
I do.
Actually, hold on.
This is costing a lot of mana.
90 mana.
Okay, that's why.
Shit.
We don't have the budget for that.
We don't have the budget.
We could try this.
This is going to be crazy.
Oh, that sucks.
Cool.
Let's get rid of this again.
Right.
So what's happening now is it's shooting a triple, which is one.
Oh, but wait a minute.
This is making it want to wait.
So that shouldn't be one of these in here.
Man, I wish I just had a spark bolt.
Just a simple as spark bolt.
Oh, wait, I need to check the perks.
Just don't take that.
Check the perks.
See what we got.
Also, I want this.
What it... Oh, okay.
This doesn't reset.
I thought it reset.
Okay, okay.
From now on, I'm going to be much more wary of doing that then.
I thought this one reset after every holy mountain.
Chordyceps.
Explosion immunity.
That's good.
Living on the edge.
Your spells deals three times damage when you're under 25 HP or 25% of maximum health.
Oh,
but I gotta go with my boy in explosion immunity.
I mean, come on.
My boy.
I mean, we gotta go with that.
That's gotta save our lives at some point for sure.
If I now add this here, what then?
Oh, wait, I also fucked this up, by the way, I need to fix it again.
I did some things.
Uh, I think I just had this here or something.
What?
What'd I do?
Oh, because I have...
Oh, wait a minute.
Fuck, dude, my heart.
That just scared the crap out of me because I shot... Look at how fast it is.
That's nuts, by the way.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Okay, I think... What?
Huh?
What's happening?
Okay, so here's my theory.
I think I sort of... I don't want to say broke the game, but I discovered a crazy combination of spells here.
And the gods are like, uh, uh, uh, you're taking it too far.
You know, the gods are angry.
But since I have this perk, they look the other way.
What the fuck?
Okay, I don't know what's happening, but I like it.
Let's just try again.
Bro, this wand is nuts.
I... Holy shit!
Look at this!
Look!
I never go...
Okay, so the gods are not angry now.
Wait, what is this?
Holy shit, it's the spider!
I'm here!
I thought there was one more level in between.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, uh, okay.
Wait a minute, this one though.
This one though.
Oh wait, it's limited too.
I have to be careful there.
It's limited.
I think I do want this.
Let's not overdo it.
It's already pretty good, you know, but I... Oh, let's just have a small taste.
And now it sucks, see?
Suddenly it's...
Something just exploded in the distance.
Uh, how did I do it?
I'm not ready, I'm not ready.
Whoops, didn't mean to pick that up, but I guess we did that now.
It's fine.
So we have healing again now, that's good.
Oh, we have another energy sphere.
Nah, I'll leave it.
Now the delayed spell cast.
Let's try that one.
It's a static projectile.
So that makes me scared.
Oh, it's also a shuffle one, so let's be careful here.
Uh, let's throw some stuff away that I don't want.
I don't want this, for example.
I also don't want Giga Death Cross.
Uh, no.
I mean, I'll try it some other time, just not this time.
This run is going to be no Giga Death Cross, whatever that is.
I don't like this one either, I don't think.
Um,
doubles, sure.
Okay, so now we're gonna try...
Which one am I gonna try?
No, not this one, this one.
There, there.
Here's to make some space.
Let's see how this works.
Interesting.
Cast three extra spells.
Which spells though?
Do I have to specify them?
Is that how this works?
One, two,
okay.
Weird.
I guess if you want to bait enemies around corners, you can sort of plant a little time to bomb and make something go off, you know?
Maybe have something insane at the payload of this, so to speak.
You could put like this one.
Oh, let's be careful.
I don't have infinite spells now.
I need to... I don't have the refresh.
So let's test this next time.
I mean, I guess it's just one.
Let's try it.
Oh wait, this is a modifier.
So we need to...
Did it, did it make eight copies?
Oh, cool!
Literal firework.
And then we do this.
Holy shit.
Uh, yeah, okay.
What if you put the thundercloud at the end of that?
That is the craziest trap to set, isn't it?
We can even put a heavy spread on it at the end.
Not that it would make too much sense.
All right, that was fine.
Now I know what that does.
I do definitely want my healing thing.
That's fine.
Now this one down here, 0.08, 0.60.
I wonder if this is actually a better one for this stuff.
Let's try just for fun, to move everything down here.
Let's see what happens then.
I mean, maybe it's hard to tell because so much shit is going on.
It's hard to tell what the hell is going on, but definitely slower.
Okay, okay.
The spiders are here.
The spiders are here!
On God, bitch.
They duck through.
Oh, this is... Oh, I hate this place already.
I hate this so much.
You got fucked up.
This one is no joke.
Oh man.
Okay, so the last one I want to make before we go, I want plasma.
But put that there and then we can do something down here because when I use my heal, let's say I've used all my heal.
Oh, it doesn't work like that.
Just use bum bum and then bum bum, right?
So...
I don't know.
Maybe just leave it like that for now.
Oh wait, this one needs to be fixed as well.
Wait, what did I have on this usually?
I had to cut... I had to cutter and then I... You know what?
How about we actually do this?
Let's have some fun here.
Here's my question.
If this one runs out and is zero and I have another spell here, if this then will turn out to be start affecting the spell over here when this one is empty, I guess we'll experiment with that because then I'm gonna do that.
And that is... this is a mess.
This is just a... click the button and see what happens.
Maybe you get lucky type of deal.
Healing, plasma, yes.
Crazy wand is number three.
No wait, put healing on there.
Crazy wand is number two.
Also, do I want to buy more?
I don't think I do.
Yeah, I don't think I do.
I'm good.
Let's get the fuck out of here and kill some spiders.
We don't have a choice.
Wait a minute.
The holy temple is intact.
The gods look the other way.
What's going on?
Bro, this wand is cracked and I love it.
Dude, I can... wait a minute, can I go back every time now?
Wait a minute.
Holy shit, I can... I can go back and change my wands.
Holy crap.
Oh, that's sick.
What the fuck?
Formation trifurcate.
Dude, wait a minute.
I'm just gonna take that.
Can I then go back?
Oh my god, look.
This is broken.
Why can't I do this?
What's happening?
I don't... I'm not gonna question it.
Fuck it.
It's happening.
This is nuts.
Okay, we got a really... Oh, you got fucked up.
What's up, spider?
You like my wand?
Dude, there's so much recall on this wand.
I'm being like, flung back.
That's nuts.
Nasty critters.
What is that sound I'm hearing?
I hear a water creature of some sort.
Nice.
There we go, baby.
Hold on, four.
Whoopsie daisy.
Goddamn, I love this wand.
This is my favorite wand ever.
Holy shit, that was a worm.
You see that?
A worm came out.
That's a sta... that's a statue right there.
Oh, that's a mine.
Blow it.
Wow.
Uh, mushrooms incoming.
Hey, spider.
You're like...
Okay,
we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine.
Calm down.
Okay, play it safe.
Take it easy.
One step at a time.
Okay, take it easy.
We're gonna play patient, precise, all that.
What do we have?
Weakening curse, explosives.
Target hit by a projectile takes 25% extra explosion damage for a time.
That sounds sick!
Uh, I am gonna take that and bring it back.
I'm totally abusing this right now.
I don't care.
Okay, let's remember, I go right to get back to that wand.
Just go right as much as I can.
Yeah, it's right here.
Why is this not fucking...
So now I can be really picky.
I'm actually gonna throw away some stuff here.
That one, that one.
Leave it.
Leave this.
You know what?
We're gonna do non-glowing lands this time.
We're doing no glowing lands.
Maybe that one can go away as well.
And I mean, I'm just gonna deposit all this shit here.
That actually could be sick having all these magic arrows or whatever.
Okay.
And I just... Dude, this is insane that I can just do this and then...
Damn.
Insanity.
Insanitor.
Oh, I didn't even see this growth.
Fuck it up.
Oh wait, there are spiders inside.
Oh, it's their little spider nests.
This is where they are being grown.
I don't like that.
It makes me uneasy.
Okay, keep going right.
Wish I had my teleport wand.
Here it is.
So, live there.
What do we got here?
Oh dude, I can just go back and grab the all-seeing eye actually.
Just to have it here.
I don't have to have this on me right now.
I can just...
Kill.
You know?
That would be pretty cool to do.
But let me just explore a little bit more first.
Also, why do I have... I have two invisiblium potions.
I gotta remember that I have that.
Oh, there's other stuff up here.
Water, water, water, water.
I have no water.
Oh, water, water.
God, I was panicking.
That was bad.
I should have really realized I didn't have any water before that happened.
Gotta come prepared.
Gotta be prepared.
What a wand.
I feel so powerful, you know?
What a feeling.
And you know what?
I don't need bombs because I have the plasma.
So what I'm gonna do is throw that away.
Actually, I don't want that.
Put this up.
Do I even want this?
Maybe I don't want this.
And then in here, I'm gonna put the all-seeing eye.
Oh, here.
Bam.
There we go.
Now I get to see everything.
All right.
Spiders, show yourself.
I'm not afraid.
I'm mentally prepared for this.
No matter what comes at me.
He throws mines.
Interesting.
What's that?
Oh, you're dead.
You are dead.
Stop throwing mines.
It's really not okay.
Fungal Caverns.
Oh no, this is the fucking place.
The air feels extremely humid.
Magic arrow with trigger.
Interesting.
That could be cool to have, I think.
But I'm gonna leave it for now.
Yeah.
Kind of wish I had that perk now where I heal with the wands.
Do I even want to go in here?
This place was nuts last time.
You know what?
I'm gonna try another path this time.
Fuck this Fungal Cavern bullshit.
I'm going somewhere else.
That place was absolute hell.
Gold for me.
Oh my god, more.
Yes.
Any spiders?
I'm getting music.
Where does this fire come from?
What the hell?
Oh, all the barren soil is burning away.
Cleanse these spiders.
God, that's so satisfying.
Oh yeah.
Boink.
All seeing eye.
Another worm came out.
It died before it could do anything.
Yo, look at this.
That's the ultimate digger.
Uh, kind of want that.
But which one do I re- maybe this one.
Let's try it.
There's no bullshit here, right?
It's just, it casts two perspell.
You know what?
I'm gonna go back and put it in a wand that just only shoots one perspell.
How about them apples?
By the way, I learned at work the other day.
I was sitting heavy in conversation with my co-workers.
Two of them are from the states.
One is from Boston and the other one is from Las Vegas.
Or just Vegas, I guess.
And I used the phrase, how about them apples?
Quite a lot.
And they're like, you know, people don't actually say that, right?
Like, really?
Isn't that a real thing?
Nope, that's not a real thing.
Am I crazy?
I feel like that's a real thing.
I've been saying it forever.
It's also said in Good Will Hunting.
A movie in Boston.
Boston, you know?
It's totally a thing.
I feel like I was taking crazy pills.
Oh wait, I've been here.
Okay, go down here.
What is that?
I don't like this growth.
I feel like I should take care of it.
There we go.
I've taken care of it.
It is now being cleansed.
I am the cleanser.
Wait, this is actually pretty chill.
Where are the spiders?
What's that?
Oh, nothing.
That's a vine.
It looked like it was alive.
You never know in this game.
I just do this with my mouth, with my mouse when I shoot.
I also do it with my mouth.
That's another story.
Damn.
Die!
Blood, blood, verta, verta, verta.
Excuse me.
Can I gain access to this wand, please?
The holy bomb!
Remember I found that and I never found it.
I couldn't use it because the wand didn't have enough mana.
Now I can finally try it!
Quadruple spell!
Here we go!
Boink!
How big?
Holy shit!
I mean, I went to a safe distance, like more than I thought I would need.
And I did the right thing.
I was expecting something ridiculous and I got something even more ridiculous.
I feel like I don't want this plasma.
You know how I said I should never replace the plasma?
I'm gonna replace the plasma.
I have black holes.
Everything's dandy, baby.
We don't need plasma.
Not where we're going.
Oh, we can go through.
This will take me to somewhere I've never been.
But I'm not gonna do it.
I am greedy.
I want to explore more of this place.
What the fuck was that?
It just fell from the sky.
It fell into the acid, so that's whatever.
Oh, it's one of these guys.
Okay.
Fuck off!
I'm on fire.
Okay, we're fine.
We are fine.
Okay, thought it was alive.
I want to find more tablets!
I want lore!
Tell me about the gods and the alchemists.
I see spider.
Fuck you!
Funny how it works, right?
When you are so powerful, spiders don't scare you anymore.
Dragon cave?
Say what now?
Excuse me.
Dragon cave?
Dragon cave.
Well, good sir.
Can I gain access?
Oh wait, is my...
Wait, actually?
Wait, is my field affecting?
Why is it so slow?
Last time I shot this, it went like...
Dragon cave.
Wait, is this a giant egg?
I'm scared.
I have an idea.
We're gonna holy hand grenade this shit.
Then we get the fuck out of here.
Boink!
Bye-bye!
See you, bitch!
What happened?
I'm scared.
Okay.
More.
That explosion, though.
I'm so scared of what's inside of here.
What's that?
Something's moving there.
You see it?
Oh, it's smoke.
Never mind.
Shoot that shit!
Shoot that bitch!
I got it!
God, that was scary.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I have two... What is this?
Extra max... Bro.
Extra max HP.
Yes.
Thank you.
What's this?
Fireball orbit.
Okay.
I killed my first boss, I think.
That's awesome.
Dude, a thousand mana?
This wand is sick!
Am I crazy?
That wand is insane.
Uh, basically, here's what I want to do.
I want this wand, but I also want the black hole.
So I'm gonna go back to base and make the perfect wand.
Oh, dude.
Let's try to remember where this is.
It's basically in the bottom right.
Right?
Because look, the wall is here.
Yeah.
So that's easy to remember.
I'm coming back.
Uh, maybe I take this wand with me now.
Then I come back for the black hole wand after.
Actually, does that make sense?
Hold on.
If I go back, I just...
No, it makes more sense to bring the other one first.
Bring this first.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're gonna go back.
It's just up.
Up, up, up, up, up.
I killed my first boss, bitch.
God, that feels good.
I'm ready for you.
I saw you there.
Nothing can scare me.
Let's not get too crazy.
Still played patiently.
Wait, I'm not going where I've already been.
This is that little risky what I'm doing here.
I guess I can explore a little bit.
But where's the way back?
Uh, what was that?
Oh, that was probably just gold.
That was about to blink away.
Where did I come from?
Nice.
Man, where did I...
Definitely not from here because there's a wand.
Let me just see what that is, actually.
A personal tentacolor.
No.
Oh, I've been here, I think.
I've not.
Shoot that guy.
Oh my god, did you see the reaction there?
Oh my god.
That was instant reaction.
Okay, let's go back.
I guess I must have come from the bottom then.
There's no other explanation because everything is dark up there, so.
Let's go here.
I believe this is the spot.
Spiders come out.
I have to remember that.
Spider.
Blow that up.
Just for fun.
Okay, so that's where I've already been.
That's nice.
Okay, so I went this way.
Oh, it's gonna be hell to get back to that wand, isn't it?
At least there's no enemies.
I think we're close.
Okay, somewhere here.
So we are here.
Question, is it right or left then?
This is the thing.
I think it's... it's gotta be left.
Here it is.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Beautiful.
Okay, so the plan is... what is the plan?
I mean, I don't need an infinite amount of these, I guess.
I think that's okay.
Oh wait, I have healing.
I'm gonna heal.
So I completely forgot I had healing.
600, dude.
That's nuts.
Okay, throw away the empty ones.
Uh, dude, so here's the question.
Does a man really need that many holy bombs?
You know, part of me really wants it.
But the rational side of me is like, you don't need this.
You don't.
You don't need this.
But you could do some amazing digging with that.
Just saying.
Part of me kind of wants to not have any black holes and just go all out with the holy bombs.
You know?
Uh, I'm just gonna deposit a bunch of these here.
Like that.
This is actually not a bad want.
In fact, isn't this one straight up better than this one?
Like, if I were to do the exact same thing, how is this not straight up better?
Oh wait, it shoots two spells per cast.
Never mind.
I don't like that.
That messes with my math.
Back we go.
So this want, uh, throw it down.
Now we go grab the, uh, the other want.
Uh, wait a minute.
Maybe I... Wait a minute, quadruple spell.
Let's put this up here.
In fact, let's put that there.
Let's put stuff that I don't think I'm gonna use somewhere.
Oh, you know what?
Maybe that one would be okay to have.
This one?
No.
I don't like that either.
The heavy spread is questionable.
Let's put it here.
Don't think I'm gonna use that either.
I like having these.
That's nice.
Uh, the weakening curse to explosives?
Uh, I mean, that could be pretty good as well.
It's just gonna make all this much better, right?
The healing, obviously, we need.
Let me see here.
Let's just organize things a little bit.
That seems good.
We have a quadruple, a triple, and two... Oh, we have two triples and one double.
Damn.
That's insanity.
The blood though?
Let's try it.
What does the blood do?
Wait.
Oh, I was so confused.
It literally shoots blood.
And charges go out super quick.
I mean, verta, verta, verta.
Not now.
Verta later.
We don't want verta right now.
And then I think I'll be happy with just a bit of these.
You don't need to go too crazy.
Maybe three.
We can have three of these and three black holes.
How about that?
That seems good, doesn't it?
Energy sphere is probably also something we can throw away.
This one also...
That one, let's keep it.
That one can go here.
And all of this...
This is a mess.
Let's leave that there for now.
Let's go grab the other wand.
Just down and to the right.
Down and to the right.
That's all we need to do.
Probably should have brought some black holes with me, actually.
Just if we need to do some digging, right?
But let me also do this.
So I went all the way left around, I think, and then down.
Yeah, this looks right.
Here.
This wand that I found on here, it looked insane.
Like the stats of it, you know?
Oh, that's my plasma.
See a plasma.
Oh, don't go in there.
Here it is.
That was easy.
Limits the radius of a projectile's explosion heavily.
It increases damage.
I mean, it's not going to affect anything on these because these are not explosions, but...
Ha!
Oh, they're all on a timer.
That's funny.
You know what?
Let me go inside of here again.
I need to see what's going on.
Now that this motherfucker emerged.
Okay.
Looks the same, it seems.
That was fun, though.
That was very unexpected.
What's with all these energy orbs?
Like, what is going on?
All right, now I want to go back up.
And I actually have a plan.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Oh, no, it's the spells cast too.
Oh, I thought this was... Oh, no.
Ah,
that just ruined all of my plans.
I did not see the mine.
I was too much in depression just now.
God damn it.
Okay, let's focus, focus up.
Let's go back and fix this once and for all.
Well, I just spent a bunch of time, or wasted a bunch of time because I thought this one was actually good.
But I guess I can still use it for something.
It does cast two spells at a time.
I guess it is what it is.
We can probably make something out of it still.
It's just not exactly what I was hoping, that's all.
Okay, here we are.
This is the entrance.
Fucking shuffle ones.
I have too many of them.
This one is a non-shuffle.
How many slots?
13.
Ah, wait a minute.
Let me...
I do actually like this, the concentrated explosion.
I feel like that's a cool skill or spell.
Replace it with that.
Oh, this is also two spells per cast.
What the fuck?
The thing I hate about the two spells per cast, I'm barely understanding the one spell per cast combinations you can make, right?
So adding the two on top is just like a headache.
It's crazy.
What would I love to make here though?
I can do things.
I think I want to experiment with these ones.
Like a bunch of the lances, the green ones.
Let me throw some stuff over here for now.
In fact, all my black hole stuff can go right there for now.
Let's remember it's right here.
Ah, no!
Get it again.
What?
Just organize things a little.
This is a mess, I know.
Ah, okay.
Grab some more of these now.
Good.
Throw this away.
That's the trash pile over there on the left.
And we have this crap.
That one.
Give me a bit more.
Sick.
Look at all these fucking magic arrows.
I think that could be really cool.
So if this shoots two per right, that would be kind of crazy.
Let's see what happens.
I mean, it's not bad, honestly.
We can make that even better.
We can quadruple things.
Wait, what did I just do?
Oh, I accidentally... So that'd be one, two... Wait, this is triple.
That's quadruple.
One, two, three, four.
And the fourth one is going to be a triple.
One, two, three.
The third one is going to be a triple.
This is one shot then.
Now that's a shotgun.
Damn.
That's actually wild.
Actually, it's even more than that because it shoots two at a time.
So I need to remember this.
This one, it doesn't do what I think because I already forgot about this part.
So in reality, what it's doing is... I actually can't do that.
Like what is going on?
It's shooting this one and that one at the same time.
And then it goes on?
That's so weird.
That is insanity.
And I can probably make it even more crazy.
Let's see.
One, two, three.
What if we do...
Whoops.
No, no, no, no.
I want that there.
Let's put this one, two, three.
Yeah, I can't do the calculation with the two.
It's just insanity.
But a thing you can do, I guess, is if you really wanted, you can always put this and it will decrease the attack speed.
Yeah, look.
It's actually doing weird things.
Oh, I also have this in here.
Yeah.
But this one is too good.
Gotta leave that.
It shoots two, two, two, two.
I remove that.
Bum, bum, bum, bum.
That's a decent amount of damage, I guess.
And if I do this...
Yeah, that's not good.
Don't like it.
All right.
I'm not sure what I want to do with all these things yet.
It's still up in the air, you know?
Maybe I'll take more of these.
And it shoots two per.
That's not something that's good, you know?
I'm overwhelmed, guys.
There's too many options.
I am struck with indecision.
I simply don't know what I want.
You know, it's just too much.
I need to keep going.
Otherwise, I'll lose my mind.
Let's just take some of these with us.
Take some for the road, you know?
And let's also take some of these just for the road.
I believe we can make crazy shit out of this later.
In fact, why don't I just do this?
Hold on.
Oh, I like that a lot.
I think I like it more.
Fuck these energy spheres.
Yes, yes.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
So throw these shit away.
And then in this one down here, I'm actually gonna...
We probably don't need that many.
One, two, three, four.
Let's have four of these, you know?
The rest we can sort of fill out with...
This is gonna be our...
black hole wand, I guess.
But the thing is, it shoots two at a time.
Maybe I should just take another wand for that.
This one also...
It's shuffled though, but it only shoots one, so that's something.
Maybe I like that more than... It's crazy, I know.
Let's get rid of these first.
I'll put it here.
No, the wand, the wand.
Ah, shit.
Here we go.
That one.
Fill this one up with all the goodies, you know?
This is our storage wand.
And maybe I'll alternate it.
This is insane.
Storage wand!
Then we can grab some extra stuff from here, and then we move on.
I want to stay here forever.
I kind of like having these different things here.
It can probably do some stuff later, right?
I can even grab this.
We even have more, that's insane.
Maybe I'll take this one.
All right.
So what should I have in my second wand?
I have healing, I have the crazy wand.
Ideally, that would be a teleport wand, right?
But I don't really have the means for that right now.
So maybe it'll just be an empty shit wand.
I mean, I could storage things in there, I guess.
It could be a storage wand.
It's just a storage wand.
I don't want that.
I do want this.
There.
Throw this away.
And then over here, I'm going to grab some of this stuff.
Bunch of storage.
Oh, sure.
Put that there.
And then we fill up the rest of this wand with that and these.
Oh, that's empty.
Throw it away.
This holy mountain is a mess.
All right, let's go.
Let's fucking go.
Now remember, don't use the second wand.
In fact, is it?
Maybe we'll just do that.
It's not going to hurt anything.
Put that up there.
So that when I use the second one, at least nothing bad is going to happen, right?
Okay.
All right.
So now I think I just want to go through the portal.
I think it's time.
Through the portal we go, in fact.
Oh, it's shuffled.
Yeah, right.
So I'm just going to...
Ah, shit.
It's going to be a little bit of a gamble.
This is going to be...
That wand is dangerous.
That one is dangerous.
Here we are.
Let's go.
I have never been this far.
It is the furthest away from home I've ever been.
God damn, these cost a lot.
Whoa, what's that?
What the hell is that?
Huh?
Let's find a good wand.
Ah, 1600, but mana charge is shit, and it also has no slots.
Yeah, these are these ones are not... Oh, this one though, but it's shuffle.
Why is shuffle a thing?
I don't understand.
It's so bad.
I hate the shuffle.
I think I want this just because this looks intriguing.
Let's try it.
Flamethrower.
A stream of fire.
Oh, yeah.
No shit.
That's what it is.
They weren't lying.
Got it.
Oh, you know what?
This can be my new healing wand.
Boop.
This one goes away, boink.
And then I grab my other wand again.
Boop.
Change slots.
Oh wait, can I not?
There we go.
Ah, whoa, whoa, whoa, down you go.
Healing.
This needs to be number two.
All right.
Man, I think I'm ready to just keep going.
Oh, perks!
What perks do we get?
Rage-fueled levitation.
Killing an enemy makes you replace some of your levitation power.
Yo, that's sick.
Angry ghost.
An angry spirit comes to your aid.
Copying nearby.
No.
Oh, I don't like any of these.
I should have checked this before I spent the money on the wand.
Fuck.
See, now the question is, when I leave here, will I still be able to go back?
Because I'm thinking, can I save up money and come back here now?
Because it didn't collapse last time.
I need to pay attention to what is different this time.
I think this is good.
You know what?
I'm gonna do a test here.
I'm gonna leave this place now without taking a perk.
I want to see what happens.
There's two things that are gonna happen.
Either this place is gonna collapse and I'll find out whether or not that will remove these perks forever.
Or if I, if, you know, I need to test that.
Or the mountain doesn't collapse and everything's fine.
So either way, it's gonna be an experiment.
I don't like these perks that much anyway, so that's what I'm gonna do.
In fact, I could be really smart here.
I'm almost max HP.
I could just not take that right now and come back here.
Because even if the stuff does collapse, I can just come back, make a hole through it.
Bam!
Deal up if I need to.
There we go.
I'm an idiot.
I should have used my heal first.
Shit.
I just realized.
God damn it!
I was being a genius and then I was an idiot at the same time there.
Let's see what happens.
And where even am I?
So okay, it does collapse.
Oh, wait a minute.
I
never went up here last time.
I, there was a hole here.
If I had made a hole here and gone this way, would that have still done it?
Oh, wait.
And also look at the perks.
They still are there.
So that's nice.
The issue is though, this is a shuffle wand and a holy bomb right here would be...
Let's do it.
Oh!
Yeah!
Okay.
Wow.
This stone is really resistant.
That worked way better than I thought.
Okay, so I'm gonna save up some money.
I'm gonna come back.
Fuck yeah.
The vaults.
This looks like Easy Base.
Am I crazy?
Easy.
What's up, guys?
Oh, wait.
Oh, never mind.
I thought this whole place was underwater, but I just went into the water.
What's up, man?
Oh, he's like a... What the hell?
Is he bleeding lava?
Damn.
Okay, that's lava.
I don't want to risk... No, no, no.
We're not taking that money.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, wait.
Actually, we have water.
Pee on it.
We're fine.
What is this?
Molten metal?
Oh, cool.
What is that?
Oh, I hit lava.
It hurt.
Bro, I think there's more recall on my wand now that I changed some of them for the magic lands.
Oh, this is like some kind of sewer.
This is very sewer-like.
Blow it up.
I fucking love this game.
This is just incredible.
Kill them all.
Kill these nasty sewer beasts.
Sir?
Oh, wait.
These are the ones to spawn?
Just like the other region.
I have no water.
Uh, I do have water.
I do have water.
See, why didn't I fill up this water bottle here?
You're asking yourself, right?
And the answer is I don't have an answer.
I was being a doofus.
A real dummy.
Uh, do I want to go this way?
Whoa, that's cool.
The black hole sucks enemies in.
Hallelujah!
I fucking love that thing.
It is incredible.
This is definitely some kind of, uh, ancient rotted away version of Heezy Base.
Is this Heezy Base version one?
What the hell was that?
Oh, that's a laser.
What's happening there?
Probably don't stand in that is what I'm thinking.
That'll be bad.
Destroy that shit.
Okay, that explodes.
Good to know.
Kill that guy.
Oh, it spawns little guys.
I forgot about that already.
Because I'm an idiot.
Goddamn, the recoil on this bastard is incredulous.
There's way more recoil with the magic missile.
It's like a little brewing station.
Shrater, bro.
Wait, what just happened?
Did I take damage?
Oh, I... that took damage.
Never mind.
What's up, guys?
The good thing about this one being so inaccurate at long range is that it's easier to hit these small guys with it.
Holy shit.
Oh, look at that.
Frostbeast.
What the hell is that?
What?
This place is nuts.
But I love it.
Okay, how am I gonna get in there?
I guess I can just pass him when he stops doing the thing.
Go.
Kill it.
It's gonna explode.
Yep.
What's this?
Giant spitter bolt, double spell, thunder charge.
Critical plus.
Oh.
Oh, this one is sick.
That's actually a sick wand.
I kind of like that wand.
I like it more than this wand.
In fact, I'm just gonna take it instead of this wand.
0.10 spells cast wand is looking good.
Yes.
Thank you.
Fuck you.
Who's up there?
This is the guy that was up there earlier that I decided not to kill at that moment.
And I have paid for it now.
Next time when I see something like that, I'm just gonna straight up kill him.
I saw him hovering here and I thought, nah, he's not gonna hurt me.
And then he came back later.
And what do you know?
He hurt me.
This wand is insanity.
Oh, that's a mine.
Shit.
Clever girl.
Don't even know what's going on there.
In fact, I have enough money to try the thing in the holy mountain.
I'm doing it.
Ah, we need to...
Wait, it's gotta be...
am I being dumb right now?
Hold on.
Good.
Then I can stand here.
Yeah.
Yeah, boy.
Let's see if it works.
Oh, it works.
That's awesome.
What's this?
Extra life, one off.
Ooh, that's...
Gamble?
No.
Stainless armor.
You take 50% less damage as long as you have no active stain status.
Ooh, man, all of these sound good.
But respawning with 100 health isn't really that much.
This is basically equivalent to me just getting an extra 100 health if you think about it.
I know it's not exactly that.
I think I want this.
50% is insane, especially when you have a lot of HP, which I do.
I believe in myself.
I'm taking the stainless because I am stainless.
But you know what?
I'm probably going to eat those words when I die, inevitably, because then I would have survived whenever that is.
So I know I'm going to feel regret when I finally do die, you know?
But I shouldn't feel like that because maybe I would have died much earlier if I didn't have this perk.
That's how I should think about it.
What's up, guys?
How's it hanging?
That little ghost, what is that?
Hello?
Yay!
Okay.
You know what's smart about this wand?
I can actually gain lift by shooting it down.
I should have thought about that when going back to the holy mountain.
I can literally just go like this and go up fast.
Oh, the music.
I like this place.
Look at all the machinery.
Oh, this is getting interesting here.
This guy has a wand.
See, I'm so afraid now I'm gonna...
This is for you.
Oh, it didn't hurt him?
What the hell?
I think he died.
Oh, oh, we got one of those guys.
I remember those guys.
We saw him in the jungle.
Oh, he's got nothing on this wand, though.
What do we have here?
Oh, I ran out of levitation.
Okay, what's this?
Vault rock.
Interesting.
Toxic sludge.
That means we can water it.
Why is it not spreading all the way?
It's like it's... mix it?
Hey, mix it up!
I can't believe that actually works.
Fucking hell.
This game is just incredible.
That's a mine.
Oh, that's electrified.
You saw that?
Whoa, what is going on up there?
Yo, they're fighting each other.
God damn it.
Things are popping off right now.
Everything is electrified.
This is nuts.
Ah, I'm on fire.
These little guys, I hate them.
Where are they coming from?
Stop.
Oh, he's hiding behind that little pipe, huh?
The little guys are the ones that fucked me up the most.
Little froggies or whatever.
Oh, what is that?
It's a blue sniper.
I almost feel the recoil in my hand.
It's hard to explain.
It's like my hand is moving to the right when I shoot.
I'm this much affected by it.
Physical recoil in real life.
So what is this?
Aiming arc.
A projectile rotates towards the direction you're...
Oh, like a laser guided missile.
Um, I don't think I want it though.
Not right now.
Oh, what the fuck?
I'm on fire.
This is a crazy area.
What?
That's... it's legitimately hard to control my character because of the recoil on this thing.
Like, I just... especially when I'm oily.
Like this, I'm oiled up, you know?
I just slide everywhere.
Hold me up, Scotty.
Shoot all the explosives.
Eliminate all potential hazards.
Give me this.
Get away from me.
Boink.
I think he's dead.
That's one way to make sure they're dead.
There's actually a guy in there.
I think it's time to have some fun.
Boink!
Can't get enough of it.
Oi!
You may think that this wand can only shoot for so long because I only shoot it in bursts.
It's only because of the recoil.
I can shoot this forever.
If I want to.
This guy is actually a crazy scary guy.
Never mind, he's not.
God, I'm loving this.
This is the coolest shit.
I'm so happy you guys recommended this game to me, man.
This is actually so good.
What's that?
Glass.
Okay.
We have a little thing up there.
Get rid of that.
Is that blood potion?
Okay.
Get away from me.
I don't even know where I'm going.
Actually, standing next to a wall like this is actually kind of smart.
Because the recoil just pushes me into the wall.
This is like I'm a little gunner.
I'm a sentry gun when I stand there.
Oh, that looks dangerous.
Man, if I had a fire trail on this, I could set fire to all this gas.
That's actually a thing I need to consider.
That would be smart.
Oh, who else
wants some?
You want some?
Oh my God.
Fuck going out of here.
I can't believe how good this wand is.
I made it so early too.
Phew.
Look at the recoil and I fly to the moon.
Man, some really technological music here.
Dude, this is actually a way to float.
Look.
I don't need my levitate.
I'm not even holding my hand on the keyboard.
I'm just using my mouse.
That's fucking hilarious.
Wow.
Insanity.
Hey, my dude.
Oh, what the hell is that?
Whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Was that a spider?
Hello.
What's your deal?
Bye-bye.
Uh, I don't like the sounds that's making.
Oh, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is, it is.
Oh, God.
Can I kill these guys?
I'm afraid.
Why am I going in there?
What am I doing?
Oliver, stop.
Don't do it.
Loki lair.
Yeah, no, yeah.
You know what?
I think I saw something down here I wanted to explore.
I'm just going to go this way.
Yeah, definitely down here there was something of interest.
Uh, a caterpillar.
Whoa, what the hell?
That was a neat little explosion.
Oh, I'm on fire.
Water myself.
Actually, I'm running low on water here.
The next time we see water, we're going to grab it and fill up our water bottle.
And then we're going to fill up our tummy.
I'm burning again.
We made it.
I'm a sentry gun.
Recall can affect me.
Mix it.
Water.
Let's go.
Whoa.
Oh, wait.
I'm, I'm explosion immune.
Forgot about that.
This is great.
Wow.
Nice.
Let's do the, let's do one more heal.
Oh yeah.
Probably could have waited with that a little bit.
Better be safe than sorry, right?
What is going on up there?
These are enemies.
These are new enemies.
I can't speak.
Okay, that explodes.
Good to know.
I need to check.
Now I know.
Those things release a bunch of oil.
Good to know.
All, let's just assume all robots explode in oil.
What a mess.
Give it like gold.
Oh, there's so much gold.
God.
Plate safe.
Calm down.
Take a moment.
Have a sip.
I actually completely forgot about my I'm so completely immersed.
Moving on.
I go up here now.
What's that?
Does that explode?
It does.
A blue ghostbuster.
A red ghostbuster.
Mine.
A hand.
Double high five.
Hey, sir.
Where'd you go?
In fact, I need to not be stained.
Then I take less damage, right?
Uh oh.
Get rid of the oil.
What do we have here?
I thought I just gained access to some secret vault type deal.
I mean, I am in the vault, but still a vault within the vault.
Let's just rest here for a sec.
There we go.
Yep.
Taking care of.
Oopsy daisy.
I'm drunk, it seems.
That means I'm flammable.
I'm burning again.
Uh, sir, that's for you.
Early Christmas present.
I think he did.
What's this?
Teleport!
Finally!
I'm definitely exchanging this.
Yeah.
Fuck yeah.
Awesome.
Oh.
Broken wand.
Do I want that?
Maybe I do want that.
How about we throw away one of the invisibility potions that we have?
I'm taking that.
Doink.
Uh, what is that?
Oh.
Let me in.
Oh, wait.
I'm immune to that explosion.
Kind of want to try just standing next to the bomb.
Is that crazy?
Is that going a little too far?
Hold on.
I'm going to try and stand here.
Don't kill me.
Nice.
Yo.
It's the ultimate combo.
That's awesome.
Oh, there's wands everywhere here.
Uh, how do I... Oh, shit.
All right.
Well, that works.
That works.
Health.
Nice.
Okay.
Yo, what the hell is this?
Bloodlust.
A projectile gains a hefty damage boost, but it's also able to hurt you.
Ooh.
I mean, honestly, that sounds fine with me on this one.
These things are never hitting me.
Right?
Remove explosion.
Pinpoint of light.
Liquid detonation.
Yo.
That sounds freaking awesome.
Oh, man.
Oh, I don't know what I... Okay.
You know what?
We don't need teleport.
We don't need that.
I've been doing fine without it.
Don't need no stinkin' teleport.
Definitely want this instead.
What's going on here?
Whoa!
That's acid.
Why is there... Oh, there's a gun.
Oops.
Someone
shooting at me?
Heavy shot.
Greatly increases the damage done by a projectile at the cost of its speed.
Ooh.
That also sounds great.
Fuck.
Ah.
Hold on.
I need to deal with this guy first.
Oh, that catches fire.
I don't know if I like having slower projectiles.
I like that they're fast.
That they hit my target, you know?
I'm gonna keep it like that.
There's a guy in there.
Hold on.
Let's take him out of his misery.
Oh, come on.
There we go.
Beautiful.
Oh, I still catch fire, so I gotta be careful about that.
Man, I'm earning cash.
Cash money.
Getting to the green.
What?
I could go through,
but I'm greedy.
I want to see what else is in here.
Another portal.
Hold!
That's a homing.
All right.
Well, you can shoot the projectiles, of course.
Okay.
Whoopsie-day.
That was a guy falling from the sky.
Also, I'm not intending to go through just yet, because I still gotta try to see if I can heal back at base.
Got him.
I'm rich.
Sup!
This is how I traverse now.
In fact, I got a, I got a, I got a logic bomb in here.
Yes!
Beautiful!
What's this?
Oh, a bunch of shit.
Sparkbolt with timer?
Magic arrow?
Okay, it's not actually that cool.
0.07.
Fortune?
Nah.
Nah, leave it.
Not that cool.
What?
Oh, it's steam!
It's not water!
Oh, crap!
My water potion is a lie.
Lovely music.
Seems we've reached the, the left end here.
Maybe there's more.
Maybe there's a little cave.
Oh, wait.
Oh, wait, there's this.
Do I want to go in here, though?
I do have a crazy weapon.
Let's quickly take a peek.
Let's just have a quick peek in here.
Oh, nice!
Good thing I did.
And you know what?
If I see something, I can just holy hang grenade it.
Fucking nuke it from orbit, you know?
We're not afraid.
Oh, no, not these guys.
You know what?
That's actually gonna be a pain to deal with without teleport.
I kill things fast, though.
So, there's that, right?
There's that.
I need to be on the lookout really slowly here.
As soon as I see a cloud, I shoot.
So, wait a minute.
Does this mean this leads back to the previous area?
Because I was in here before, wasn't I?
Oh, you know what?
I don't like this place.
No, I'm leaving.
I don't like it.
I feel like this is gonna be the end of me.
We're moving on.
In fact, I just want to go through the portal.
I want to see what's next.
Shit, shit, shit.
Oh, wait.
No, I have to go up first.
Because I want to try and heal at the holy mountain before I move on.
Sweet.
Is that... that's toxic sludge, okay.
I can't tell the difference, man.
I feel like, okay, maybe as it is a bit more green, higher contrast green.
Like, no, like this?
No, this is also toxic sludge.
What the...
Oh, that thing is bad news.
Just straight up, straight up, straight up somewhere.
So, the question is, is the left or right?
I think it's right.
Am I wrong?
Hey, I mean, I've definitely not been here, but I have been in here, it seems, so...
Why is this not going in a straight line?
I don't understand.
Usually, is it because of my...
I think it's because of my field.
My projectile field.
That... it has to be the thing that's doing it.
Ah, here we are, here we are.
Perfect.
Here we are.
Nice.
Made it.
Because then we can heal here, and we can save the heal in the next one for when we need it.
Yeah, dude.
That felt so good.
And I can't change my... I know, I can't change once now.
So, when this collapses, that's it.
That's the... that is... that is indeed it.
You know what?
Let me try and explore more to the right.
I need water.
I don't have it.
Let's find some water, huh?
Man, I'm poisoned for a long time.
Oh, this is bad.
Oh, that was terrible.
You definitely need water.
But I guess down here, finding water is a little difficult.
It's the goddamn sewer.
By the way, it's called the vault.
Speaking of... there's water right there!
The vault.
What are they vaulting in here?
You know, that's what I want to know.
What are they hiding in here?
What are they protecting?
What are they vaulting?
Yeah.
I need to know.
Keep going.
We're gonna go all the way to the right here.
And then I'm gonna go straight down and check the wall.
How?
Wait, why is there a...
What?
Huh?
A worm has been at work here.
Yo!
Ha!
Cool.
All right.
Wait, what's this?
Why is there a little...
teleportation?
Wait a minute.
Shit!
Oh wait, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Oh wait, this doesn't destroy this anyway.
What about the black hole?
Uh, right.
Okay, weird.
I wonder if that little bucket of teleportation underneath is the reservoir that the portal is using to send people somewhere.
Maybe it's like teleportation, but focused on a specific point.
You know, usually teleportation is unstable.
And when you use it, you just get somewhere.
But if it's down there in that little vat, it was right beneath the portal.
It's what's fueling the portal and the portal is focusing in, so to speak.
To a certain place, right?
I don't think I realized what I had made when I first made this wand.
Like earlier today, I didn't realize the power of this.
Let's go a little bit more this way.
Launch up.
That works.
Nice.
What the hell is this?
A bunch of rotten meat.
Bro, that is... we have to blow this up.
We can't let this stand.
Hold on, actually.
How about that?
Yeah, okay, dude.
Oh, come on.
Oh!
Hallelujah!
I was actually gonna use a holy bomb here, but okay.
I'll take it.
Dig.
Am I out?
Oh, I'm out of everything.
Okay.
Well, it was fun while it lasted with that wand.
It was fun while it lasted.
See ya.
Hey, man.
Oh, that hurt.
Get out of here.
Man, I can't really get into... get in here anymore.
Is he bleeding diamonds?
What the hell?
Wait, do I have... I have hand spasms.
Okay.
Look at all these wands, dude.
Wish I had my bombs now.
Whoops.
I'm just hiding in my little hidey hole.
Wand.
A bunch of magic bolts.
Man, these wands are going crazy.
2500 mana.
Not that you really need it when you have infinite mana like this wand, but... All right, cool.
Pretty cool.
What do we got over here?
Haha, the blood's better.
Wait, what?
Where the hell are we now?
Charm on toxic sludge makes a projectile charm creatures covered in toxic sludge.
That sounds way too specific, but this is pretty much all around a better wand than this one.
Oh, but it doesn't have as many slots.
What is this?
The digging bolt.
That's actually really good too.
But no, not right now.
Man, this place goes hard.
I feel like I've been here.
A chest.
Oops.
What's that?
Formation behind your back.
We can encourage electricity.
25% extra damage.
Thank you.
Yeah, I have almost 5000 gold.
This is insanity.
I guess I get to reroll a bunch of perks.
I will take it.
Oh, he hit me with the teleport thing.
That's actually scary.
That's one of the things that could really fuck me.
My plasma cutter is back.
I don't want it though.
I have holy hand grenades now.
Ugh, stuck.
Why am I not getting a name for this place that I'm in right now?
Come on now.
Oh, there's so many of them.
Look at that.
What is this?
What the hell?
Bring it on, bitches.
I dare you to come through this hole.
I feel like I'm shooting so fast the audio is bugging out a little bit.
I'm just surprised how stable this game is.
When you think of all the inter-connecting elements of this game and how much shit is happening and all the physics being simulated, it's unreal how stable this shit is.
Oh, look, they wobble.
Can I not kick it?
Oh, that's an enemy.
He was hiding in the real fungus.
That bastard.
Uh, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Wait a minute.
Oh,
what is that even?
Some kind of look like a chest almost flying around.
Uh, don't want to go down there.
Okay.
Ow.
Stop it.
Bring it on.
Dude, I'm in the zone.
Who's shooting that?
You are doing that.
My hand spasms.
Dormant crystal with trigger.
Holy shit.
No.
I don't even want to know what that looks like.
That scares me.
What the hell is that?
Freezing gaze.
A heart freezingly sinister aura.
I want to try that.
Uh, okay.
Cool.
I guess.
I guess you can really shotgun this in close range if you multicast it.
Would be kind of nice.
I'm going to keep going right.
Shit.
I'm teleporting.
I was scared there for a second.
I gotta admit that that scared me.
That's, that's a mine.
He's shooting mines.
What else we got here?
Oh, wow.
This is becoming Saturday.
This fucking run right here is insane.
That's how you take care of those guys.
And all their spawn.
Got him.
I think it's time, dude.
We go through.
All right.
Let's wait with that.
Holy shit.
That's expensive.
What?
Are you kidding me?
Chain bolt, plasma beam bounce.
Circle of water.
Dude, arrow for 3000.
What the hell?
Lava to blood.
Oh.
That sounds useful.
Let's try and see that.
Oh, wait, why did I do that?
Perks.
No, I forgot enemy radar.
You can sense nearby enemies.
Extra want capacity.
Oh.
Oh, I thought I gained an extra like up here.
Oil blood.
You bleed flammable oil, but are immune to fire.
See, I don't know about that, because wouldn't that mean I get stained all the time?
I mean, I wait, when do I ever bleed?
Do I bleed a lot?
I haven't noticed.
I don't think this is good because I'm pretty good at sensing enemies to begin with.
I could also come back and recharge or like restore this.
Oh, you know what?
I'm going to test this now.
So I have the perfect thing to test.
Also, let me just test what I just got.
Makes any lava within a projectiles range turn into blood.
That sounds pretty dope.
Honestly,
not bad.
Take this and then I want to use a heal because this one heals.
Okay, before I do that, I want to test my theory here.
So watch this.
I am going to go over here now.
I want to basically make a hole here.
Oh, look at these guys.
That's not going to do anything.
Oh, so maybe this is actually a good.
Oh, it did make a small hole.
What the hell is that?
Nasty critter.
Make the other one.
Motherfucker.
We try again.
There we go.
Oh, the gods look the other way.
Huh.
Oh, wait, I think I understand now.
I get it.
Okay, so yeah, I'm definitely right.
Look at this.
So I made a hole through, right?
Yeah, look, I can go through.
What the hell is that?
So watch.
Yep.
So here's the thing.
Okay, the gods, this is a temple to the gods.
It's a holy temple, right?
The gods are unhappy when I don't follow the rules of the gods.
The gods is, if I go the normal way, then I can't go back and do the thing, but now I've done this and I have technically angered the gods, but I haven't because I have the perk that makes them okay with it.
So there it is.
Mystery solved.
That's actually really cool.
And in a weird way, the gods here could be seen as the developers.
If you think about it, the developer intended for me to go this way, right?
And have everything be blocked behind me and have me not be able to do the things that I can do here anymore.
And then I'm like, nah, fuck that.
I'll make my own way out, you know?
And the gods are like, we don't like when you break our game, but uh, so we're angry now.
We're going to send you this thing to kill you.
I don't know if there's anything to that, but that's just what I imagine, you know?
The gods are angry.
The gods could be the developers.
Uh, I'm going to come back here for that.
So let me do a heal now.
I'm going to do this.
Look how much that heals.
It's definitely a percentage type heal.
It's not a flat heal because this didn't heal that much last time.
Where the fuck am I?
Temple of the art.
I even got an achievement there.
I usually have a steam overlay turned off because I hate it.
I guess I forgot to turn it off, but I got an achievement just now for this.
Oh my, they have some HP now, huh?
So the art, we know about this.
We found a tablet about the art.
Oh man.
Oh, I'm excited.
Wait a minute.
Are those black holes?
They sure are.
Look at that.
They have little tablets with art of black hole.
That's a crystal.
Here's the thing though.
I am so excited about this, but I'm saving and quitting.
I just realized, by the way.
Oh, nevermind.
Nevermind.
Everything's fine.
Okay.
I need to, uh, I need to eat, of course.
Man, this was, this was, this was something, wasn't it?
I did so well today.
Okay.
I'm opening jet.
The first thing I see is he's going to die so fast next time.
Watch me.
Okay.
Watch next time and find out.
Cause I'm going to rip this game to shreds.
By the way, guys, no deaths.
Wasn't that impressive.
Five hours, four and a half hours, I guess.
No deaths.
God, today I feel like a winner.
You're a gig a big brain.
Yeah, I was.
I don't know what you're referring to.
I think I know what you're referring to.
And thank you.
True gamer.
Oh, you're also proud of me.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
You got a machine gun wand.
I fucking do.
That wand was cooking the enemies to perfection.
Wasn't overcooked.
It was just the right amount.
Fantastic.
Hold on.
I, the wizard, have mastered this game.
That's all I wanted to say.
Wait a minute.
Did I actually die once today?
And you're saying the first death doesn't count or did I not die at all?
I don't remember.
Did I actually, was it actually true no death?
I didn't die, right?
I didn't die.
Fuck yeah, that's sick.
That's actually amazing.
I played so patiently.
Did you do some gambling?
What do you do when you see a spider on your wall in real life?
Depends on the size of it.
Luckily, in Denmark, the spiders are not that big.
There was once I saw a really big spider and I couldn't do it.
Luckily, it was at my parents and I had my dad take care of it.
But I couldn't even like pick it up or smash it or do anything.
I couldn't even touch it or do anything.
Just the thought of killing it because it's so big also makes me so uncomfortable is no.
But if there's a normal sized spider, I can deal with it.
I'm getting goosebumps still.
I'm getting like the chills, but I can usually grab a piece of cloth and take it.
It's not like I can't do anything about it.
I don't have arachnophobia or anything like that.
At least I don't think so.
I think people that have that are truly scared to death of it.
I don't think I have a true phobia of it.
I'm very uncomfortable with them.
That's all.
Yeah.
The doubters lost their money in gambling today.
There it is.
Teaches you not to doubt me.
I had so much trouble getting that sentence out for some reason.
You were sad you didn't do the gamba.
What is a gamba?
Gamba?
How about them?
Okay, guys, how about them apples?
Let me ask you.
Is that a real saying that people say?
Oh, gamba gamble.
Ah, okay.
I didn't... Ah, okay.
Didn't know that.
Only twitch enjoyers.
I say it now.
But they... Matt Damon says it in Goodwill Hunting.
He says that.
Yeah, I've heard it before.
Not allowed to gam... Oh, wait.
Are some people not allowed to...
But it's not like real... It's like pretend gambling, though.
Like, it's not real money, right?
So there's... I don't know what the... Okay, that's interesting.
Depends on age and region if you use that saying.
It is a real expression.
Yeah, okay.
Thank God.
Even if it wasn't, I would still be saying it.
I love saying it.
How about them apples is real?
Yeah.
I can gamble, but only with cereal potatoes.
You can imagine winning or losing, you know?
You could, I guess, keep a tally of it if you wanted yourself on a little piece of paper.
Maybe because point redeemable can have real life rewards.
Oh, that makes sense, Ducky.
Ducky Burt.
That makes a lot of sense.
Good point.
Yeah.
You never heard of it?
I thought it wasn't an American expression, though, Hyogo Nomichron.
No, wait.
I think your name is Hyogo Nomichron, right?
I butchered that the first time.
Imagine the payout of gambling on what?
It's probably about the addictive nature of...
Yeah, okay.
That makes sense.
Even if it's not real money, you know?
Are they supposed to be cosmic potatoes?
I don't know.
I just... I had a whole black and white thing going.
There's no real meaning behind it.
I just liked how they looked.
But you can imagine that being a little, you know, cosmic thing with stars inside.
It's full of stars.
Astro... Kind of looks like an asteroid, actually.
That's a good point.
I like the asteroid interpretation.
I want potatoes.
Ah, man.
It's actually too late to go to the store.
I do have some food at home, but I'm gonna eat that.
But I would like to actually get some potatoes.
Okay.
Thank you guys for watching, subscribing, and following, and just chatting and hanging out.
It's super cool.
Today was awesome, man.
Somehow this game keeps getting better.
And somehow there's even more and more content.
It's insane.
This is amazing.
So, yeah.
Thank you so much for recommending this to me.
I would never have gone for this game if it wasn't for you guys, I don't think.
So, I really appreciate it.
You're the best.
Good night, people, and I'll see you next time.
Have a good one.
I'm gonna send you off.